On the Unstable SMP,
在不稳定SMP上，
我们俩要迎战一千名玩家大军。
I'm about to fight an army of 1,000 players all at the same time,
我唯一的队友，竟是我的死对头，
with my only ally in the coming battle being my greatest rival,
Flamefrags。
Flamefrags.
[Flame] 有啥战术不？
Um, so any strategy going into this?
[Wemmbu] 赢就完事了，兄弟。
Win, bro.
[Wemmbu] 我搁这儿刷怪呢。
I'm just farming them in this.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀！
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这也太爽了！
Dude, this is amazing.
[Flame] 先干掉这个。
Kill this guy.
[Flame] 什么情况？什么情况？
What the, what the?
[Flame] 漂亮！
Nice!
[Wemmbu] 对了，我刚看见了一个鞘翅重锤哥。
Oh yeah, I just saw an Elytra Mace.
[Wemmbu] 他刚从旁边飞过去。
He just passed by me.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀，我简直了...
Oh my god, I just...
但要明白为什么Flamefrags会和我联手，
But to understand why Flamefrags and I would ever team up,
以及为什么一开始就有一千人来追杀我们，
and why 1,000 players would even hunt us in the first place,
我们得回到战斗开始之前。
we need to go back to before the battle even began.
事情是这样的，
You see,
过去一个月，在这不稳定的SMP上，
for the past month on the Unstable SMP,
我演了一出完美的金蝉脱壳，
I've completely faked my death,
彻底隐姓埋名。
going under a false identity.
因为自从我成为最强玩家，
Because ever since I became the strongest
在战斗中击败Flamefrags后，
player when I defeated Flamefrags in battle,
我就无事可做了。
I've had nothing left to do.
但Flame从不相信我真的死了。
But Flame never believed that I was truly dead.
所以，
So,
他花了一个月追捕我，
he spent a month hunting me down,
系统地耗尽了我所有的物品和资源，
systematically draining all of my items and resources,
最终拿到了我还在世的确凿证据，
eventually obtaining undeniable proof that I was still alive,
以及我的真实身份。
and of my true identity.
这一切只是为了能和我再打一场，
All so he could have a rematch with me,
以最终确定谁才是
in order to determine once and for all who the
不稳定SMP真正的最强玩家。
strongest player of the Unstable SMP truly is.
[Wemmbu] 好吧，
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 过去三天我就像
well I just spent like the last three days
[Wemmbu] 被鹦鹉抄家了一样，资源都被榨干了。
getting all my resources drained by Parrot
[Flame] 我才不在乎别人觉得你比我牛，
I don't care people believe you're stronger than me because
[Flame] 不就靠你那笨重锤和破核弹赢的我吗？
you use your chungus mace and your stupid nukes to beat me
[Wemmbu] 是啊，我确实挺厉害的。
Yeah, well I kinda am.
[Flame] 不，
No,
[Flame] 你要真觉得自己最强，那就大错特错了。
you're not if you really think you're the strongest
[Flame] 就像你说的，对吧？
Like you said, right?
[Flame] 强者必胜。
The strongest will win no matter what.
[Wemmbu] 好吧，我想你是对的。
Well, I guess you're right.
[Flame] 今晚布罗迪酒吧见。
Oh, Brody's tonight.
[Flame] 你好。
Hello
[Flame] 够高了。
High enough.
[Wemmbu] 你知道，
You know,
[Wemmbu] 我就在上面坐20秒，等缓降生效——
I'm just gonna sit up here for 20 seconds while the slow fall tries-
[Wemmbu] 等它——好的，谢了兄弟。
Waits to- Okay, thank you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 谢谢。
Thank you.
[Wemmbu] 不，谢谢。
No, thank you.
[Flame] 又给你加了30个。
Another 30 for you.
[Wemmbu] 行，我们打持久战。
Alright, we'll play the long game.
[Flame] 拜托，别这样。
Dude, come on.
[Flame] 有胆下来单挑啊，兄弟。
Come down here and fight, bro.
[Wemmbu] 你才是那个用缓降的赖皮鬼。
You're the one using freaking slow falling.
[Flame] 是啊，
Yeah,
[Flame] 因为你根本不懂为啥要用那些蠢诱饵——
because you wouldn't know why you're using stupid baits on-
[Wemmbu] 你上次都没用缓降！
You didn't use slow falling last time!
[Flame] 神级战利品。
OP loot.
[Wemmbu] 神装。
[Wemmbu] 谢了，兄弟。
Thank you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟！
Bro!
[Wemmbu] 真香。
Delicious.
[Wemmbu] 我怎么刚看到一条消息？
How did I just see a message?
[Flame] 啊？什么？
Yeah, what?
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 我爱缓降！我爱缓降！我爱缓降！
I love slow falling! I love slow falling! I love slow falling!
[Flame] 兄弟，这又不是我的错，是你在用——
Dude, it's not my fault that you're using-
[Wemmbu] 是你在用！都怪你！
You're the one using it! It is your fault!
[Flame] 放下重锤我就不用了。
Just put the mace down and I'll stop using it.
[Flame] 天啊，我简直是个神射手。
Oh my god, I'm a- I'm a sharpshooter.
[Wemmbu] 呃，
Uh,
[Wemmbu] 嘿，
hey,
[Wemmbu] 嘿，伙计，
so buddy,
[Wemmbu] 呃，
uh,
[Wemmbu] 外面大概有五十个人。
there's like 50 people outside of here.
[Flame] 什么？
What?
[Flame] 我没看见——
I don't see-
[Wemmbu] 哟，我还以为你想——这家伙是谁？
Yo, I thought you wanted to- Who is this guy?
[Flame] 我不认识他。
I don't know who he is.
[Flame] 谁啊——喂，
Who is- Hello,
[Flame] 兄弟？
bro?
[Wemmbu] 哦，好吧，所以要开打了。
Oh, okay, so we're fighting.
[Wemmbu] 哦，原来是你。
Oh. So this is you.
[Wemmbu] 所以你只是一个——好吧，
So you're just one- Okay,
[Wemmbu] 我还以为你不是这种人——
so I thought- I didn't take you for-
[Wemmbu] 我没看出你是个骗子。
I didn't take you as one for a liar.
[Flame] 兄弟，我的天啊。
Bro, oh my god.
[Flame] 什么？
What?
[Flame] 他们是执法者，老兄。
These are lawmen, dog.
[Wemmbu] 执法者？
Lawmen?
[Wemmbu] 好的，
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 我还是——我——我没在攻击你！好吧，
so you're still- I'm- I'm- I'm not attacking you! Alright,
[Wemmbu] 看来我们还得接着打，
I guess we're still fighting,
[Wemmbu] 然后。
then.
[Flame] 是的，我们就是在打。
Yes, we are.
[Flame] 我的天，不。
Oh my god, no.
[Wemmbu] 呃，嘿，他们人太多了。
Uh, hey, so there's like a lot of them.
[Flame] 我的天，老兄。
Oh my god, dude.
[LettuceK] 好久不见。
Good to see you.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 干掉Flame！干掉Flame！你怎么——好吧
kill Flame! Kill Flame! How are you- Okay,
[Wemmbu] 他们也在杀我！
so they're also killing me! You're alive?
[LettuceK] 你还活着？
[Wemmbu] 你看，
You see,
[Wemmbu] 在我假死之前，
before I did the whole fake death thing,
[Wemmbu] 我好像大概也许是把LettuceK的整个执法基地给炸了。
I kinda maybe sort of blew up LettuceK's entire law base.
[Wemmbu] 所以，
So,
[Flame] 我的——看，
my- Look,
[LettuceK] 兄弟，
bro,
[LettuceK] 看，
look,
[LettuceK] 天降正义！等等，
it's raining justice! Wait,
[Wemmbu] 这些家伙是在——哦，
so are these guys at- Oh,
[Wemmbu] 下雨了？
it's raining?
[Wemmbu] 哦，所以你也要打我？
Oh, so you're attacking me as well.
[Wemmbu] 等等，我对你做了什么？
Wait, what did I do to you?
[LettuceK] 兄弟，你把我整个基地都炸了！
Bro, you blew up my whole base! I did do that.
[Wemmbu] 我确实干了。
[Flame] 我的天——好吧，
Oh my- Okay,
[Wemmbu] 哟，
yo,
[Wemmbu] Flame，
Flame,
[Wemmbu] 你——好吧，
you- Okay,
[Wemmbu] 现在你想暂时停战吗，
now do you wanna put the fight on hold,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟？
bro?
[Flame]当然，这搞什——我的天。
I'm sure, what the- Oh my god.
[LettuceK] 我也很震惊你还活着。
I'm also- I'm just shocked that you're alive.
[LettuceK] 我还以为——我以为你就这么消失也太便宜你了。
I thought- I thought it'd be too good that you just vanished.
[Flame] 我们直接干掉他们吗？
Are we just killing them?
[Wemmbu] 嗯，直接干掉就完事了。
Yeah, just kill them.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 好的，
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 不过这地方太狭窄了。
this is like a really confined space though.
[Wemmbu] 搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
[LettuceK] 好了各位。
Alright, guys.
[Wemmbu] 嚯，我肯定用重锤砸到你了。
Oh, I just definitely maced you.
[Flame] 是吗？
Did you?
[Flame] 想弄死我吗，老弟？
Are you trying to kill me, dog?
[Wemmbu] 不，我没有！
No, I'm not!
[LettuceK] 好了，你该拿上那个——
Alright, you should be taking the-
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 我的勇士们！
my braves!
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 这里的实体怕是有1500个吧。
there's like 1500 entities here or something.
[Wemmbu] 你想用这个对付我？
Were you gonna use this on me?
[Flame] 哦，是啊。
Oh, yeah.
[LettuceK] 哇哦。
Ooh.
[Flame] 我可不会碰那个。
I wouldn't take that.
[Flame] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 哟，我们直接溜吧，老兄。
Yo, let's just run, dude.
[Wemmbu] 就像，
Like,
[Wemmbu] 我们真在乎杀这些人吗？
do we even care about killing these people?
[Flame] 兄弟，我们可以快速解决他们。
Bro, we can just kill them real quick.
[Wemmbu] 哟，你该不会——
Yo, are you-
[Wemmbu] 好吧，但如果我们真想打，
Okay, but we're just gonna like burn materials
[Wemmbu] 只会白白消耗材料。
if we wanna actually fight.
[Wemmbu] 直接跑路吧。
Let's just run.
[Flame] 呃，你确定吗，老兄？
Uh, are you sure, dog?
[Flame] 不知道。
I don't know.
[Wemmbu] 是的，直接离开。
Yes, just leave.
[Wemmbu] 直接离开。
Just leave.
[Wemmbu] 直接走人。
[Wemmbu] 他们能怎样？
What are they gonna do?
[Wemmbu] 跟着我们？
Follow us?
[Wemmbu] 漂亮！
Yeah!
[Wemmbu] 谁干的？
Who set that up?
[Flame] 快点！
Hurry up!
[Flame] 我的天啊。
Oh my god.
[LettuceK] 你们就这点本事对付我？
Is this really what y'all do on me?
[Wemmbu] 大伙儿？
Y'all?
[Wemmbu] 为什么有人到处送纪念碑啊？
Why is there like a guy that just gives monuments each other,
[Wemmbu] 比如...
like...
[Wemmbu] 酷哦。
Cool.
[Wemmbu] 我要淹死了。
I'm drowning.
[Wemmbu] 这简直太棒了。
Like, this is just amazing.
[Wemmbu] 我的天，这招居然管用。
Oh my god, that actually works.
[Wemmbu] 哈哈。
Haha.
[Wemmbu] 为什么他们要杀我？
So why are we killing me?
[Wemmbu] 我跟这个Flamefrags什么的压根没关系。
I'm not even related to this Flame frags whatever.
[Wemmbu] 我做什么了？
What I do?
[Wemmbu] 我的意思是，我确实干了，但我的意思是。
I mean, I did in fact do that, but I mean.
[LettuceK] 你还屠过城？
And you've wiped out entire cities?
[LettuceK] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[LettuceK] 你可真是个正直的人。
you're a real stand-up guy.
[Wemmbu] 那颗末影珍珠飞哪儿去了？
Where did that pearl go?
[Wemmbu] 再见！
Bye!
[Wemmbu] 等等，
Wait,
[Wemmbu] 这不就是那个黑曜石穹顶嘛。
so this is genuinely just the obsidian dome.
[Wemmbu] 这太蠢了。
This is stupid.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Wemmbu] 还有...
There is...
[Wemmbu] 哇，我好像什么都耗尽了。
Wow, I'm just like fully out of everything.
[Wemmbu] 我们不可能还在认真打吧。
There is no way we're seriously doing this still.
[Wemmbu] 我的天，老兄。
Oh my god, dude.
[Wemmbu] 就像……
Like...
[Flame] 好的。
Alright.
[Wemmbu] 呃，
Uh,
[Wemmbu] 那个...
so...
[Wemmbu] 我们不想先处理那支大军吗？
Do we not want to handle the giant army first?
[Flame] 他们不在这儿，对吧？
They're not here, are they?
[Flame] 开打。
Let's fight.
[Flame] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Wemmbu] 你果然还带了把激流三叉戟。
And of course you have a Riptide Trident also.
[Wemmbu] 我这么努力图啥？
Like, why do I even try?
[Flame] 天啊，搞什么鬼。
God, the fuck.
[Flame] 花招啊，兄弟。
Tricks, bro.
[Flame] 想下来吗？
You want to come down?
[Wemmbu] 各位。
Everybody.
[Flame] 兄弟，我早该猜到是你
Dude, I should have knew you were this
[Flame] 兄弟，兄弟。
inbid, dude, bro.
[Flame] 当你狂按那些...
When you spam those...
[Wemmbu] 网泡恶魔！
The web bubble demon.
[Flame] 重锤飞天怪！
The mace flying off demon.
[Wemmbu] 是啊，可惜我没带火箭，所以...
Yeah, well, I don't have any rockets, so...
[Wemmbu] 有点挑战性。
It's a little challenging.
[Flame] 来吧，兄弟。
Come on, bro.
[Wemmbu] 呃，
Uh,
[Wemmbu] 我觉得大军回来了，
I think the army's coming back,
[Wemmbu] 因为我刚看到一条线索消息。
because I just saw a lead message.
[Flame] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 你知道吗？
You know what?
[Wemmbu] 我们一起补货吧，兄弟。
Let's just group restock, bro.
[Flame] 集体补货。
Group restock.
[Wemmbu] 当然，好啊，好啊。
Sure, yeah, yeah.
[Wemmbu] 行，我现在就干掉你。
Alright, I'm killing you now.
[Wemmbu] 哇，我末影箱里
Wow, I don't even really have
[Wemmbu] 也没多少东西了。
Much stuff in my E-chest.
[Wemmbu] 哦，不错，不错。
Oh, cool, cool.
[Wemmbu] 来啊，兄弟。
Come on, bro.
[Wemmbu] 呃...
Um...
[LettuceK] 嘿，
Hey,
[LettuceK] 大伙儿。
guys.
[LettuceK] 我们在干什么？
What are we doing?
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 话说，
so,
[Wemmbu] 天才，
Genius,
[Wemmbu] 我们又打起来了，
we started fighting again,
[Wemmbu] 然后他们就跑这儿来了。
and then they just came here.
[Wemmbu] 你指望会发生什么？
Like, what did you expect to happen?
[LettuceK] 等等，那我们这是在干什么？
Wait, so what are we doing?
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 就像，
Like,
[Wemmbu] 为什么是我？
why me?
[Wemmbu] 怎么又是我？
Why me?
[Wemmbu] 为什么在所有还活着的人里偏偏是我，
Why me out of everyone that's still alive,
[Wemmbu] Flame？
Flame?
[Flame] 你什么意思，为什么是你？
What do you mean, why you?
[Flame] 你能干掉一个让我们抢点装备吗？
Can you kill someone so we can get some gear?
[Wemmbu] 你能干掉一个吗？
Can you kill someone?
[Wemmbu] 我没力气了。
I have no strength.
[Wemmbu] 我啥也干不了。
I do nothing.
[Flame] 给，想要力量吗？
Here, you want strength?
[Flame] 想要力量吗？
You want strength?
[Wemmbu] 是，是，我想要力量。
Yes, yes, I want strength.
[Wemmbu] 求你了。
Please.
[LettuceK] 不，别让他拿到力量。
No, don't let him get strength.
[Wemmbu] 能给我力量吗？
Can I get strength?
[Flame] 扔药水！扔药水！
Pot it! Pot it! Oh my god, I hate you.
[Wemmbu] 我的天，我恨死你了。
[Wemmbu] 我就在你旁边。
I was right next to you.
[Wemmbu] 扔药水，扔，扔，扔，扔。
Pot it, pot, pot, pot, pot.
[Wemmbu] 谢了。
Thank you.
[Wemmbu] 我的天
Oh my god,
[Flame] 干掉一个！他们好像有，
kill someone! They have like,
[Flame] 顶级装备！
top gear!
[LettuceK] 哟！放松。
Yo! Relax.
[Wemmbu] 靴子拿来。
Yeah, I need the boots.
[Wemmbu] 好的，你刚拿走了。
Okay, you just took them.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 靴子在哪儿？
Where are the boots?
[Wemmbu] 保护II？
Prot 2?
[Wemmbu] 太糟了。
That's terrible.
[Flame] 我才不在乎他的人。
I don't care about his people.
[Wemmbu] 不过，那是保护IV。我也带了个耐久。
Although, that's Prot 4. I was unbreaking, too.
[Wemmbu] 行行行。
Okay, okay, okay.
[Wemmbu] Flame,
Flame,
[Wemmbu] 这波能直接跑尸干回来不，
can we just run back the fight in,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 啊...
a...
[Wemmbu] 闭嘴。
Shut up.
[Wemmbu] 我们能不能直接跑回去拿装备...
Can we just run back the invi...
[Wemmbu] 我话都说不利索了。
Like, I can't even talk now.
[Wemmbu] 瞧你干的好事。
Look what you did.
[Wemmbu] Flame，
Flame,
[Wemmbu] 我们能不能直接跑回去再打一次，
can we just run back the fight,
[Wemmbu] 就像，
like,
[Wemmbu] 换个好点的地方，
at a better location,
[Wemmbu] 不受打扰，
uninterrupted,
[Wemmbu] 求你了？
please?
[Flame] 兄弟，我是说，我们没得选。
Dude, I mean, we don't have a choice.
[Flame] 就像，每次都是这样。
Like, every freaking time.
[Flame] 老兄，你能别烦我吗？
Dude, can you leave me alone?
[LettuceK] 兄弟，我已经给过你...
Bro, I already gave you...
[LettuceK] 我给过你选择，但是...
I gave you an option, but...
[Wemmbu] 哦，服务器刚才可不喜欢那一下。
Oh, the server really did not like that one.
[LettuceK] 哦，原来我们卡是因为这个。
Oh, that's why we're lagging.
[LettuceK] 怪不得会卡。
That's why we're lagging.
[Wemmbu] 就干掉了一个？
That killed one person?
[Wemmbu] 真的吗？
Really?
[Wemmbu] 死了一个？
One person died?
[Wemmbu] 不，这简直太绝了。
No, that's just fantastic.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，你知道吗？
You know what, dude?
[Wemmbu] 去他的。
Screw this.
我决定直接逃离战场，
I decided to just run away from the battle
远离Flame、执法官和所有人。
with Flame and the Law and everyone.
但到了这个时候，
But at this point,
木已成舟。
the damage had already been done.
因为不仅Flamefrags和LettuceK
Since not only do Flamefrags and LettuceK
现在知道我还活着，
now know that I'm actually alive,
而且参战的所有这些执法官都知道了。
but literally all of these Lawmen that were at the fight.
而且，就算我不知怎么把他们全干掉了，
And even if I somehow killed all of them,
就像，
like,
这怎么可能嘛，
there's just no way that that would happen
至少会有一个跑掉。
without at least one of them escaping.
所以，
So,
看来我的假身份是彻底暴露了。
it was safe to say that my fake identity was pretty fried.
即使在我经历了这么多冒险之后，
And even after all of my adventures,
不过，
though,
我还是没想好在服务器里要做什么。
I still had no idea what I wanted to do on the server.
我感觉自己又回到了
I felt like I was in the same place I was
一个月前，在我假死之前的状态。
One month ago, before I even faked my death.
[Flame] 哟，Wemmbu。
Yo, Wemmbu.
[Wemmbu] 我们绝对不可能这么做。
There is no way we're doing this.
[Flame] 嘿，兄弟。
Hey, bro.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Wemmbu] 我要用用脑子。
I'm gonna use my mind.
[Wemmbu] 走，找我我去。
Let's find me, bro.
[Flame] 你要去哪儿？
Where are you going?
[Wemmbu] 嘿，
Hey,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
bro.
[Flame] 准备好开打了吗？
Are you ready to fight now?
[Wemmbu] 不，我现在还没准备好。
No, I'm not ready to fight now.
[Wemmbu] 你觉得我们再打起来会怎样？
What do you think is going to happen if we start fighting again?
[Flame] 兄弟，我们跑得太远了。
Dude, we went so far.
[Flame] 这不可能。
Like, there's no way.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，Lettuce说他有办法找到你。
Bro, Lettuce said he was finding you somehow.
[Flame] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Flame] 嘿，
Hey,
[Flame] 兄弟。
bro.
[Wemmbu] 老兄，说真的。
Dude, seriously.
[Wemmbu] 我们能不能别，
Can we not just,
[Wemmbu] 就像，
like,
[Wemmbu] 先搞定Lettuce再打？
deal with Lettuce first and then fight?
[Flame] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Flame] 兄弟，他要溜了。
Dude, he's going to run away.
[Flame] 来啊，兄弟。
Come on, bro.
[Flame] 直接来找我啊，兄弟。
Just come find me, bro.
[Wemmbu] 好的，
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 但Lettuce又会杀回来打断我们。
but Lettuce is going to pull up again and then interrupt us.
[Wemmbu] 而且这次我们的装备会更差。
But we're going to have even less gear this time.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Flame] 你只会跑。
You're just gonna run.
[Flame] 哟，停。
Yo, stop.
[Flame] 停。
Stop.
[Wemmbu] 好吧，我不跑。
Okay, I'm not running.
[Wemmbu] 看。
Look.
[Wemmbu] 我没在逃。
I'm not running.
[Flame] 天啊！天啊！就像，当它...
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Like, when it's...
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Flame] 我的天。
my God.
[Wemmbu] Lettuce到底为什么一开始要追捕你？
Why is Lettuce even trying to hunt you in the first place?
[Flame] 兄弟，我甚至不知道。
Bro, I don't even know.
[Flame] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Flame] 我甚至不知道，兄弟。
I don't even know, bro.
[Flame] 他就是莫名其妙重新召唤了坐骑，然后开始追捕我，
He just randomly resummoned and then started hunting me for,
[Flame] 比如……
like...
[Flame] 我不……
I don't...
[Wemmbu] 当然，兄弟。
Of course, bro.
[Flame] 只是...
It's just...
[Flame] 我甚至都没完全搞懂。
I don't even fully understand.
[Flame] 就像，
Like,
[Flame] Minecraft的头号通缉玩家...
would Minecraft's most hunted player...
[Wemmbu] 不，不，不，天啊，我的裤子要坏了。
No, no, no, my God. My pants are going to break.
[Wemmbu] 不，为什么？
No, why?
[Wemmbu] 就像，谢了，兄弟。
Like, thank you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 谢谢。
Thank you.
[Flame] 不客气，兄弟。
You're welcome, bro.
[Flame] 呃，是的，他们可能很快就到。
Um, yeah, they might pull up soon.
[Flame] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Wemmbu] 我们为什么不...
Why don't we...
[Wemmbu] 好了，天才主意在此。
All right, genius idea here.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 所以，
So,
[Wemmbu] 我们为什么不先干掉Lettuce再打？
why don't we kill Lettuce and then we can fight?
[Flame] 我是说，
I mean,
[Flame] 我想是没得选了。
I guess there's no choice.
[Flame] 我是说，
I mean,
[Flame] 现在杀掉你也没什么意思。
it wouldn't be much of a fight to kill you right now.
[Flame] 嗯，估计是。
Well, I mean, it probably would be.
[Wemmbu] 你八成会输，不过嘛...
I mean, you would probably lose, but...
[Flame] 看看你手里有什么。
Look at what you have.
[Wemmbu] 瞅瞅你手里有啥。
[Flame] 呃，好吧。
Um, okay.
[Wemmbu] 那也没用。
That still doesn't matter.
[Wemmbu] 我还是打败了你。
I still beat you.
[Flame] 你真逗。
Yeah, you're funny.
[Flame] 你可真逗。
You're extremely funny.
[Wemmbu] 你什么意思，你超有梗？
What do you mean you're extremely funny?
[Wemmbu] 要不是Lettuce突然杀到，这把早拿下了。
I was winning before Lettuce pulled up.
[Flame] 根本不是这样。
That's not even true.
[Wemmbu] 你这话从何说起？
What do you mean that's not even true?
[Wemmbu] 我秒了你。
I popped you.
[Wemmbu] 我们开打五秒内我就把你打爆了。
I popped you in the first five seconds of our fight.
[Flame] 兄弟，这压根不叫...
Dude, that's not even...
[Flame] 首先，这根本不对。
For one, that's not even true.
[Wemmbu] 这怎么就不是真的了？
What do you mean that's not even true?
[Flame] 躺着摸鱼。
Lying up and being,
[Flame] 就像，
like,
[Flame] 在天上蹲点，
just camping in the sky,
[Flame] 兄弟。
bro.
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 天上蹲点。
Camping in the sky.
[Wemmbu] 这法子管用。
Yeah, that's what works.
[Flame] 技艺超群。
Very skillful.
[Wemmbu] 嗯，什么招都行，但不太高明。
Yeah, every works, but it's not good.
[Flame] 你太菜了。
Yeah, and you suck.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞。
All right.
[Flame] 你怎么就成最强了？
How are you the best?
[Flame] 你游戏玩得太烂。
You're not good at the game.
[Flame] 就像，什么？
Like, what?
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，好吧。
Dude, okay.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Flame] 什么？
What's?
[Wemmbu] 重新备装，处理好Lettuce，
re-gear, and take care of Lettuce,
[Wemmbu] 然后我们再打。
and then we can fight.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Flame] 搞定Lettuce，我就打败你。
So, we take care of Lettuce, and I'll beat you.
[Flame] 听起来挺有趣。
That sounds like fun.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。当然。
Oh, my God. Sure.
[Flame] 拿着你的风弹，伙计。
Here, take your wing charges, buddy.
[Wemmbu] 谢了，兄弟。
Thank you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 谢谢。
Thank you.
[Flame] 如果要干掉Lettuce，
If we're going to take out Lettuce,
[Flame] 那你直接来我基地。
then you just come to my base.
[Flame] 就像，
Like,
[Flame] 他还活着，
he lives,
[Flame] 就在
like,
[Flame] 离它一百格远的地方。
100 blocks away from it,
[Flame] 那，
so,
[Flame] 我是说...
I mean...
[Wemmbu] 哦，等等。
Oh, wait.
[Wemmbu] 他为什么住在离你基地一百格远的地方？
Why does he live 100 blocks away from your base?
[Flame] 兄弟，他太怪了。
Dude, he's so weird.
[Flame] 他…他专挑我去下界那天，然后就直接，
He... He waited till I went to the Nether one day and just,
[Flame] 比如……
like...
[Flame] 他只组织了百来号玩家来建造。
He only orchestrated 100 players to build it.
[Flame] 难说啊，兄弟。
I don't know, bro.
[Flame] 他这人怪怪的。
He's weird.
[Flame] 他在我家旁边盖了个巨型基地。
He built a massive base next to mine.
[Flame] 这简直是最怪的事了。
It's the weirdest thing ever.
[Wemmbu] 好的，我们开始。
All right, let's start.
[Wemmbu] 我们还有很长一段路要走。
We have, like, a really long way to go.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Wemmbu] 行啊，你非要接着打我是吧？
All right, so you're going to keep hitting me?
[Wemmbu] 好吧，
Well,
[Wemmbu] 我在等你跟上，好让我们能聊两句。
I'm waiting for you to catch up so we can have a dialogue.
[Wemmbu] 我比你快多了。
I could go faster than you.
[Wemmbu] 懂了吧？
See?
[Wemmbu] 你倒是跟紧点啊，老兄。
Yeah, catch up, buddy.
[Flame] 随便。
Whatever.
[Wemmbu] 我正想聊两句呢，
I was trying to have a dialogue,
[Wemmbu] 聊两句。
a little bit of conversation.
[Wemmbu] 嗯，我刚刚...
Yeah, I was...
[Wemmbu] Lettuce当时...
Lettuce was...
[Wemmbu] 我猜刚才我隐身的时候，
I guess when I was invisible now,
[Wemmbu] 因为现在Lettuce和那帮人...
because now Lettuce and all those people...
[Flame] 好嘞！
Yeah,
[Flame] 不
doesn't,
[Flame] 就像，
like,
[Flame] 现在大家都知道你是谁了吧？
everyone know who you are now?
[Flame] 好多人都看见你了。
Like, so many people just saw you.
[Wemmbu] 好吧。
Oh, I guess.
[Wemmbu] 我看也是。
I guess they do.
[Flame] 那差不多有20个人，外加Lettuce。
That was, like, 20 people and Lettuce.
[Wemmbu] 谢了，老兄。
Thanks, man.
[Flame] 兄弟，我不...
Dude, I don't...
[Flame] 你为啥一开始要这么干？
Why did you even do this to begin with?
[Flame] 就像，隐身。
Like, go invisible.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，我闲得慌，兄弟。
Bro, I was bored, bro.
[Flame] 你闲得慌？
You were bored?
[Flame] 就像……
Like...
[Wemmbu] 等等，我们为啥不再开个传送门？
Wait, why don't we make another portal?
[Flame] 那也不至于那么无聊。
It could have not been that boring.
[Flame] 兄弟，
Bro,
[Flame] 如果跟这家伙去下界，
if we go into Nether with this dude,
[Flame] 我们就死定了。
we're dead.
[Flame] 我是说，
I mean,
[Flame] 可以试试，
we can try,
[Flame] 但是，
but,
[Flame] 就像，
like,
[Flame] 如果在下界被看到，
if we get spotted in the Nether,
[Flame] 我们就死定了。
we're dead.
[Flame] 真没骗你。
I'm not even lying.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 不，
no,
[Wemmbu] Lettuce也在追捕我，
Lettuce was hunting me also for,
[Wemmbu] 比如...
like...
[Wemmbu] 感觉他好像...
Like, I think he's...
[Wemmbu] 我想这兄弟是想当服务器的大执法官吧。
I think bro's trying to be the big crime enforcer of the server.
[Flame] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Flame] 他惦记这招好久了。
he's been trying to do that for a while now.
[Flame] 而且这波更惨。
And it's low-key been worse,
[Flame] 因为，
because,
[Flame] 就像，
like,
[Flame] 最近，
recently,
[Flame] 比如...
like...
[Flame] 比如，
Like,
[Flame] 我跟他交过手。
I've fought him before,
[Flame] 搞定了。
and it was,
[Flame] 就像，
like,
[Flame] 五个。
five of them.
[Flame] 但是，
But,
[Flame] 喜欢
like,
[Flame] 现在他可是真的有，
now he genuinely has,
[Flame] 就像，
like,
[Flame] 成百上千的玩家。
hundreds of players.
[Flame] 就像……
Like...
[Wemmbu] 唉。
Aw.
[Wemmbu] 等等，你到底犯过啥事儿？
Wait, so what crimes have you even committed?
[Flame] 我都不记得我干过啥了。
Oh, I don't even remember what I've done.
[Wemmbu] 对咯，兄弟。
Yeah, exactly, bro.
[Wemmbu] 你可不是我这种正牌恶棍。
You're not a real criminal like me.
[Flame] 我的目标又不是当罪犯。
Well, my goal isn't to be a criminal.
[Wemmbu] 确实，这说明你还不如我呢。
Exactly, which means you're worse than me.
[Flame] 这根本说明不了什么。
That doesn't mean anything.
[Wemmbu] 这说明你不如我。
It means you're worse than me.
[Flame] 这说明你不讲武德，
That just means you have no honor,
[Flame] 而且你是个失败者。
and you're a loser.
[Wemmbu] 不，
No,
[Wemmbu] 这说明我当恶棍比你更在行。
it means I'm better than you at being a criminal.
[Wemmbu] 你的基地在哪儿？怎么走？
How... Where is your base?
[Wemmbu] 哦，等等，我知道在哪儿了。
Oh, wait, I know where that is.
[Wemmbu] 没事，我知道在哪儿。
Never mind, I know where that is.
[Wemmbu] 下雨了！开冲！
It's raining! Let's go!
[Flame] 我的天！
Oh my God!
[Flame] 我去！
既然开始下雨了，
Since it had started raining,
我们就能用激流三叉戟飞了，
we were able to Riptide Fly,
这样我们能跑得更远，
allowing us to travel much,
比以前快多了。
much faster than before.
[Wemmbu] 我…
I've...
[Wemmbu] 我去过永恒黑暗。
I've been to Eternal Darkness.
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[Wemmbu] 喂？
Hello?
[Wemmbu] 我的三叉戟快散架了。
So, my trident's about to break.
[Wemmbu] 我们是不是...
Are we...
[Wemmbu] 快到了没？
Are we almost there?
[Wemmbu] 我听不见你说话。
I can't hear you.
[Wemmbu] 谢了，老兄。
Thank you, man.
[Wemmbu] 谢谢。
Thank you.
[Flame] 我们应该非常非常非常接近了。
We should be really, really, really close.
[Wemmbu] 哦，好吧。
Oh, okay.
[Wemmbu] 等下，这该不是你的黏土山吧？
Oh, wait, is this your mesa?
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] Flamefrags的恶地。
The Flamefrag's mesa.
[Flame] 得，这玩意儿不归我喽。
Well, it's not mine anymore, I guess.
[Flame] 现在它不是我一人的了。
It's not just mine anymore.
[Wemmbu] 为啥？
Why?
[Flame] 真烦人。
Which is annoying.
[Wemmbu] 你连为啥都不知道，
You don't even know why,
[Flame] 因为执法官住在这儿。
because the law lives here.
[Flame] 跟我一起。
With me.
[Wemmbu] 那就把他轰出去。
Well, just kick him out.
[Flame] 说得轻巧。
Yeah, easier said than done.
[Wemmbu] 哦对，我的错。
Oh, yeah, my bad.
[Wemmbu] 我忘了你比我弱点儿。
I forgot that you were a bit weaker than me.
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 随便。
Whatever.
[Wemmbu] 哦，不是去他们基地那种。
Oh. Not like to their base.
[Flame] 哦。
Oh.
[Flame] 好嘞！
Yeah,
[Flame] 我都不知道我们从这边过来了。
I didn't know we were approaching for this side,
[Flame] 洛基。
Loki.
[Flame] 呃...好的，嗯...
Okay, um...
[Flame] 得当心点。
We need to be careful.
[Flame] 绕上去吧。
Oh, let's just go around like up here.
[Wemmbu] 好的
Okay
[Wemmbu] 那咱们直接冲过去把他们全宰了，
So if we just pull up there and slaughter them all,
[Wemmbu] 那咱们就...
then we can...
[Flame] 我是说...
I mean...
[Flame] 也不完全是，因为他们分散在服务器各处了。
Not really because they're spread it across the server.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀
Oh my god,
[Wemmbu] 真的假的？
really?
[Flame] 到处都这样
Like everywhere
[Flame] 好嘞！
Yeah,
[Flame] 他们老巢都被我端过一回了
I've cleared out their entire base like once
[Flame] 今天时间有点紧
and like we just got a tight today
[Flame] 显然啥也没干成
so like obviously didn't do nothing and
[Flame] 那边人好像还不少
I think there's low-key more people there
[Flame] 跟那次突袭差不多
like at the attack we had
[Wemmbu] 哦
oh
[Wemmbu] 好的
Yes,
[Flame] 我的人马。
it's my amount of people.
[Flame] 我想要
I want though
[Flame] 墙上有人。
Yeah, there's some people on the walls.
[Wemmbu] 我滴老天
Oh my god,
[Wemmbu] 真烦人。
so annoying,
[Wemmbu] 掉坑里了也没啥好说的
so there's no point in even how I fell down the hole
[Flame] 我去
my god
[Flame] 是啊，没啥意思
Yeah, there's no point of um
[Flame] 端他们老窝
attacking their base
[Flame] 谁在放水？下面有人倒水了？
Who is placing water someone has a water down there?
[Flame] 千万要小心啊
Yeah, just be very careful
[Flame] 不知道往哪走，就这边吧。
I don't know what, let's just go this way.
[Flame] 这下应该行了。
This should be better.
[Flame] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my God.
[Wemmbu] 我是说，
I mean,
[Wemmbu] 我这儿有点。
I have some,
[Wemmbu] 我箱子里有装备。
I have gear in my inner chest.
[Wemmbu] 我胸有丘壑。
I have an inner chest.
[Wemmbu] 这感觉就像，
It's just like,
[Wemmbu] 我好像少了点东西，
I'm missing like,
[Wemmbu] 我好像丢了些金苹果
I think I'm missing Gapple
[Wemmbu] 还有经验值。
and XP.
[Flame] 天哪，我可能还有一些金苹果。
Oh my, I might have some Gapple.
[Flame] 我一点经验都没有啊，兄弟。
I have zero XP bro.
[Flame] 我可不是那种料。
I'm not built like that.
[Wemmbu] 等等，
So wait,
[Wemmbu] 不过Lettuce住那个基地里。
lettuce lives in that base though,
[Wemmbu] 对吧？
right?
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 他还活着，他还活着，耶。
He lives, he lives, yeah.
[Flame] 他就住那儿，老铁。
He literally lives right there, bro.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞。
All right.
[Flame] 我基地离这儿十万八千里。
And my base is like a hundred blocks away.
[Flame] 噢，就搞这个。
Oh, we're just doing this one.
[Wemmbu] 好的
Okay
[Wemmbu] 咱们直接冲过去咋样？
What if we just like pull up there and
[Wemmbu] 就跟解决Lettuce差不多呗？
just like take care of lettuce then?
[Flame] 呃。
uh
[Flame] 我们可以去会会他。
I mean we can go there we can try and kill him,
[Flame] 但这招从来都不管用
but it never really works
[Wemmbu] 从不操心
never really worry
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 那是因为我还没试过宰了他。
well that's cuz I haven't tried to kill him yet.
[Flame] 行啊，有本事你宰了他呗
Yeah, whatever and if you do kill him
[Flame] 我直说吧
I'm gonna just say like
[Flame] 这波操作有点拉。
It's bad looks,
[Flame] 可咱们也没啥坏事可干啊
but I mean we don't have nothing to do bad looks
[Flame] 我猜你八成没戏
I mean like you're probably not going to be allowed
[Flame] 现在谁还跟商人城交易啊，瞧瞧Lettuce。
to trade a merchant city anymore like know lettuce.
[Flame] 嗯哼
Yeah
[Flame] 兄弟你上哪搞装备去
I don't know where you're gonna get gear buddy
[Flame] 哇，这么多啊。
Huh, this is a lot.
[Flame] 嗯，我刚刚——
Yeah, I just-
[Flame] 好多地方都爱Lettuce。
a lot of places that like lettuce.
[Flame] 我跟搞笑似的
I'm just like funny
[Flame] 我好像会喜欢上他们。
I'm just gonna like them apparently.
[Wemmbu] 我靠黑帮存货发家
I've seen living off the mafia stash
[Wemmbu] 好几个月了
for like yeah, months
[Flame] 兄弟，你这看着不太阔啊。
Okay, you don't look very rich, bro.
[Wemmbu] 好吧。
Well.
[Wemmbu] 嗯，好吧。
Yeah, well.
[Wemmbu] 我快把存货掏空了。
I'm at the end of the stash so yeah,
[Flame] 所以你得搞点交易
so you need to have trading
[Flame] 你还好吗？
Are you good?
[Flame] 嘿，
Hey,
[Wemmbu] 我记得这地儿
I remember it here
[Wemmbu] 有点
Kinda
[Wemmbu] 小巧更妙。
Good in tiny.
[Flame] 我觉得你右边没跑对
I don't think you ran through here the right so
[Wemmbu] 我跑过这儿
I ran through here
[Flame] 哦，好吧。
Oh, okay,
[Flame] 别杀我们，求你了
don't kill us, please
[Wemmbu] 这下我咋出去？
Well, how am I gonna get out?
[Wemmbu] 不，
No,
[Wemmbu] 只有用重锤把他们炸飞我才能脱身
the only way I can get out is if I win burst off them with my mace
[Flame] 干掉一个。
Okay, kill one of them.
[Wemmbu] 好吧
All right that
[Flame] 我说过要一个
Okay, I said one
[Flame] 好的。
Alright,
[Flame] 我都没空处理这个。
I haven't even had the time to get rid of this.
[Wemmbu] 这地儿不就是头一关吗
Hey so isn't this literally the first place
[Wemmbu] Lettuce大军会来找你算账的
that Lettuce army would look for you after
[Wemmbu] 咱逃出来了？
we escaped?
[Flame] 呃，他其实不怎么来这儿。
Ummm, he doesn't really come here actually.
[Flame] 可能吧？
I mean maybe?
[Flame] 他可能会来这儿。
He might come here,
[Flame] 我猜他有点不敢来这儿。
like I think he's kinda scared to come here,
[Flame] 笑死。
which is funny.
[Flame] 世事难料。
You never really know.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Alright,
[Flame] 我好像忘了放
I think I forgot to put
[Flame] 谢天谢地没人偷——万一——
him- thank God no one stole- what if-
[Flame] 装备齐活了，开干
Alright we're geared ya off
[Flame] 你还有另一套，对吧？
You have full another, right?
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 我只要力量药水。
I just need like strength potions.
[Wemmbu] 我浑身没劲。
I just have like, no strength.
[Wemmbu] 我差不多有，哦，还有烟花。
I have like, pretty much oh and fireworks.
[Wemmbu] 有火药没？
Like, do you have gunpowder?
[Flame] 没啥。
Not much.
[Flame] 给你点力量。
Here's some strength.
[Wemmbu] 你铅块不太够，拿着。
You have a little sparing lead, take this.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟
Bro
[Wemmbu] 等等！
Wait!
[Wemmbu] 来点糖。
I need a sugar.
[Wemmbu] 来得正好！
I needed it!
[Wemmbu] 有了！
I know!
[Wemmbu] 糟糕！
Oh webs!
[Wemmbu] 等等，我能拿点蜘蛛网不？
Wait, can I take some webs?
[Flame] 别碰我的宝贝。
No, don't touch my stash.
[Wemmbu] 行行行。
Alright fine, fine, fine.
[Wemmbu] 但我得搞点火药。
Alright, I need this gunpowder though.
[Flame] 哟，老铁。
Yo, dude.
[Flame] 我要宰了你。
I'm gonna kill you.
[Wemmbu] 我需要火药！
Well, I need the gunpowder!
[Wemmbu] 就凭你？
Like you could.
[Flame] 说得好像你能似的，兄弟。
Like you could, dude.
[Wemmbu] 甘蔗搁哪儿了？
Yo, where's your sugar cane at?
[Flame] 老兄，在外面。
Dude, is outside.
[Wemmbu] 我能拿这个长效力量吗？
Alright, can I take this long strength?
[Wemmbu] 反正你也不用长效力量。
You don't even use long strength anyways.
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 你能扛住。
You can take the long strength.
[Flame] 我一般从干掉的家伙那儿捡。
I normally get that from the people I kill.
[Flame] 杀人掉落的。
From the people you kill.
[Wemmbu] 我背包简直被卡死了。
My inventory is like so cucked.
[Flame] 你的手下在我基地里到处乱窜。
Your agents are exploring all over my base.
[Wemmbu] 老铁，我认真的。
Dude, I am.
[Wemmbu] Boosfer的房间。
The Boosfer's room.
[Wemmbu] 能开个房间吗？
Can I make a room?
[Flame] 不行！你是我基地里最没资格建房间的人。
No! You're the last person to make a room in my base.
[Wemmbu] 这盾牌真不赖。
This is a cool shield.
[Wemmbu] 胡萝卜归我了。
I'm taking these carrots.
[Flame] 哦豁。
Oh, yeah.
[Flame] 你都没发现我顺走了七套护甲吧。
I don't even think you realized but I took like seven armor sets.
[Wemmbu] 不，我其实知道，不过谢了。
No, I actually did realize, but thanks.
[Flame] 哦，好嘞。
Oh, okay.
[Wemmbu] 你的甘蔗我收下了。
Alright, I'm taking some of your sugarcane.
[Wemmbu] 我想再玩火箭了。
I want rockets again.
[LettuceK] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 嘿，
Hey,
[Wemmbu] 还记得我说过这简直是
so remember how I said that this was literally
[Wemmbu] 他们第一个搜哪？
the first place they were gonna look?
[Wemmbu] 呃，Flame。
Uh, Flame.
[Wemmbu] Flame！
Flame!
[LettuceK] 嗯...
Um...
[Wemmbu] Flame！
Flame!
[Wemmbu] 还记得我说过这简直
So remember how I said this was literally
[Wemmbu] 我本来想先搜哪儿？
the first place I was gonna look?
[Flame] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Flame] 他真在这儿？
is he actually here?
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！等等，我先去拿点...
Yes! Okay, wait, let me get some...
[Wemmbu] 我的老天。
Oh my god.
[LettuceK] 要帮忙吗？
Wanna help?
[Flame] 哟，
Yo,
[Wemmbu] 他们只打你吗
are they just attacking you
[Wemmbu] 妥
yeah
[Wemmbu] 等下，我拿个火箭。
Wait, let me grab rocket, please.
[LettuceK] 哦 别这么快
Oh not too soon
[Wemmbu] 这个我用不着。
I don't need that one.
[Wemmbu] 我干啥了？
WHAT DID I DO?
[Wemmbu] 搞什么鬼？
WHYYYYYY?
[LettuceK] 这问题我都答腻了。
I feel like I've already answered that question so many times.
[Wemmbu] Flame,
Flame,
[Wemmbu] 早跟你说这儿会先被搜。
I told you this was the first place that they were going to look.
[Flame] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 咱就这么认了？
Are we are we just taking this okay?
[Wemmbu] 咱俩在瞎忙活
I think we're just taking this
[Wemmbu] 我们再比一次
We could run again
[Wemmbu] 天呐，跟大队人马竞速太折磨人了。
Oh my god, racing big groups is so annoying.
[Wemmbu] 为啥棋盘一半是V一半是U？
What do you mean why they're half of the board V half of the board U.
[Wemmbu] Lettuce，
Lettuce,
[Wemmbu] 你从哪儿找来这么多人的？
where do you even find all these people?
[LettuceK] 深得人心
win the hearts of the peoples
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[LettuceK] 比如，
Like,
[LettuceK] 你们大杀四方的时候，
while you guys have been killing it,
[LettuceK] 干架。
fighting each other,
[LettuceK] 随便。
whatever,
[LettuceK] 我最近可猛了。
I've actually been making bold moves.
[Flame] 放手一搏。
Bold moves.
[Wemmbu] 放手一搏。
[Wemmbu] 你这话说得真够蠢的兄弟
you sound so stupid bro
[Flame] 来搭把手。
join me.
[LettuceK] 不管是我还是你。
Whether it was me or not you.
[LettuceK] 有人听见了
someone hearing it bro
[Flame] 他们被虐惨了。
They're generally getting beat so bad.
[Wemmbu] 可我连个史莱姆都打不着，
Except I can't hit a stone slime,
[Wemmbu] 不过确实挺炫的。
but it's show though.
[Flame] 但愿这些不是你的人。
I hope these aren't your fucking players,
[LettuceK] 不知道。
I don't know.
[LettuceK] 那可不。
Of course they are.
[LettuceK] 我还没动真格呢。
The near fraction of my strength.
[Wemmbu] 近在眼前？
The near fraction?
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Right.
[LettuceK] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 这感觉啊，
it's like,
[Wemmbu] 就跟切豆腐一样。
it's like putting through butter.
[Flame] 你这就是在装看不见。
It's like you're choosing to ignore them,
[Flame] 你在玩……
you're running the...
[LettuceK] 你
You're
[LettuceK] 阴魂不散。
just always there.
[LettuceK] 不过，这怎么——哦。
But, how's the- oh.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
yeah,
[Wemmbu] 他们正在
they're actively,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 不理我，直接奔你去了。
ignoring me and running to you.
[LettuceK] 你干嘛推我？
Why are you putting me?
[Flame] 漂亮。
Nice.
[LettuceK] 我是说，
I mean,
[LettuceK] 我得说，
I will say,
[LettuceK] 你还活着这游戏就没法玩了。
you being alive makes me hate this game.
[Wemmbu] 谢了兄弟。
Thank you bro.
[LettuceK] 我寻思着...
I assume...
[Wemmbu] 其实我连核弹都不需要。
Actually I don't even need nuke
[Wemmbu] 我正想问能不能用核弹。
I was gonna ask if I could nuke,
[Wemmbu] 但我真用不着。
but I really don't think I need it.
[LettuceK] 大伙儿加把劲。
Alright keep at it team.
[LettuceK] 你们队打得不错。
team you're doing great.
[Wemmbu] 他们全都
they're they're all
[Wemmbu] 要死了 你为啥要骗他们
dying why are you just like lying to them
[Wemmbu] 那人直接被射飞了
I guess oh that guy just got bowed out of the way
[Wemmbu] 这下可舒坦多了。
oh this is so much nicer when they're
[Wemmbu] 当我不存在，你忙你的
just like ignoring me and focus on you
[Wemmbu] 哟，我直接就能——
Yo, I can just like-
[Flame] 哎，老倒霉蛋了。
Yeah, this always happens to me.
[Flame] 哈。
Ha.
[Flame] 必须快到
It must nigh-
[LettuceK] 哇！
Oh!
[Wemmbu] 晚安。
Night night.
[LettuceK] 我去！
Oh!
[Flame] 能上天可真爽。
It must be nice just to get in the air.
[LettuceK] 嘿，兄弟们，搭把手呗！
Yo, gimme a hand, folks!
[Wemmbu] 这就是你们要打的大反派LettuceK。
So this is the Big Bad Lettuce K that you were fighting claim.
[Flame] 嗯，只要...
Yeah, when there's-
[Wemmbu] 我直接爽翻了。
I just popped twice.
[Flame] 俩人感觉完全不一样。
It's a lot different when there's two people.
[Flame] 我这重锤可不便宜！
And I don't have a cheap mace!
[Wemmbu] 确实。
That is true.
[LettuceK] 闪开，老兄！
Get out of my way, dude!
[LettuceK] 还好有这龟速移动。
Thank goodness for the turtle moves.
[Wemmbu] Lettuce你早该把重锤给
Lettuce you couldn't have given your
[Wemmbu] 菜鸟至少有点经验。
goons at least a little experience.
[LettuceK] 这波血赚！
That's valuable bro!
[LettuceK] 这又不是发糖，哪能见人就给。
You can't hand that out like it's candy.
[Flame] 你压根不在乎他们吧？
You just don't care about them then huh?
[Flame] 你赶紧把这货给我弄走。
You may as well just get this guy away from me.
[Wemmbu] 啥，你连他都搞不定？
What, you're having trouble with him?
[Flame] 真烦人。
This is annoying.
[LettuceK] 我搞到海龟了，绝非偶然。
I got turtles bro, it's no accident.
[Wemmbu] 我溜了。
I'm out.
[LettuceK] 你缺啥？
You out of what?
[LettuceK] 别藏着，说出来大家听听。
No speak up, share with the class.
[Wemmbu] 嚯。
Huh.
[Flame] 他们只会逃
They're just running
[Flame] 他们吓得团团转。
around, they're scared.
[LettuceK] 快上啊兄弟！别看我！
Yo, get in there bro! Don't look at me!
Oh
[LettuceK] 哦
[LettuceK] 天呐，老兄。
my god, dude.
[Wemmbu] 快上啊兄弟，快冲进去！
Yo, get in there bro, get in there!
[LettuceK] 可能就我这样。
It might just be me, guys.
[LettuceK] 但我觉得咱们人没以前多了。
But I feel like there's less of us than before.
[Flame] 我死定了，必杀无疑。
I'll killed, kill once.
[Wemmbu] 我来收拾掉队的。
I'll kill the stragglers.
[Wemmbu] 搞什么鬼？
Oh, what the heck?
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 我堆叠里的充能耗尽了
I run out of my charge in my stack
[Wemmbu] 这感觉就像穿上了别人的裤子
and it's like put on someone's pants
[Flame] 嘿伙计
hey buddy
[Wemmbu] 你把我头盔打烂了！
OH YOU BROKE MY HELMET!
[Wemmbu] 搞什么鬼啊？！
WHAT THE HECK, MAN?!
[Wemmbu] 不是吧？！
REALLY?!
[Wemmbu] 你管这叫好主意？！
LIKE YOU THOUGHT THAT WAS A GOOD IDEA?!
[Wemmbu] 管他呢。
whatever
[Wemmbu] 你血还挺厚
you got plenty of health
[Wemmbu] 你力气不小
you got strength
[Wemmbu] 我没力气了
I'm out of strength
[Wemmbu] 你从他身上碾过去了？
You run over him?
[Wemmbu] 算了，
Nevermind,
[Wemmbu] 我才不稀罕。
I didn't need it.
[Flame] 冲啊冲啊冲啊冲啊冲啊！
Go, go, go, go, go!
[Wemmbu] 哈，这比我想的简单多了。
Huh, well this was a lot easier than I expected.
[Flame] 好嘞，
Yeah,
[Flame] 俩人开黑，一个开挂。
when there's two people and one of them's cheating.
[Wemmbu] 要不我来力挽狂澜。
Or maybe I just make the big difference.
[LettuceK] 如果这能
If it means
[LettuceK] 关你啥事。
anything to you.
[Wemmbu] 略略略！
Nyah-nyah!
[LettuceK] 哦。
Oh.
[Wemmbu] 你的手下全歇菜了。
And all your goons are dead.
[LettuceK] 真的吗？
Really?
[Flame] 嘿，哥们儿。
Hey bro.
[Flame] 直接干掉他。
Just kill him.
[Flame] 干掉Wemmbu
Kill Wemmbu
[LettuceK] 你居然以为这就完了。
What's crazy is that you think this is over.
[Flame] 这怎么可能不是！
How is it not!?
[Flame] 你挂了。
You're dead.
[LettuceK] 不。
No.
[LettuceK] 你真以为有技术或火力就无敌了？
You think that it's skill or firepower that makes you strong?
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
Y-yes!
[Flame] 不行！
No!
[Wemmbu] 哈哈哈哈！
Ha ha ha!
[LettuceK] 听着，兄弟。
Look, you- listen bro.
[LettuceK] 管住人，就管住了一切。
You control the people, you control everything.
[Flame] 好嘞！
Yeah, alright!
[Flame] 你的人都归莫德管了，那就这样吧。
Most of all your people, so.
[LettuceK] 你以为，你以为我的人就这些？
You think, you think that's all my people?
[LettuceK] 看，
Look,
[LettuceK] 你们还是没把我当回事。
y'all aren't tak- y'all still aren't taking me seriously.
[Wemmbu] 我们可没在。
Yes, we're not.
[LettuceK] 但说真的，这玩意儿
But all I'll say is that this is,
[LettuceK] 这是，
this is,
[LettuceK] 大伙儿
you guys,
[LettuceK] 这没完没了了。
this is never going to end.
[LettuceK] 只要你俩还在
as long as you two still exist,
[LettuceK] 我照样会逮到你
I'll still be chasing you down
[Wemmbu] 怎么又是我？
WHY ME?
[Wemmbu] 我干啥了？
WHAT'D I DO?
[Wemmbu] 是你先抛下我的，不是我！
YOU LEFT ME, NOT ME!
[LettuceK] 哦，不妙
oh, thats not good
[Flame] 来 来 来 来 来
come, come, come, come, come
[LettuceK] 瞧，我可能正在跑路
look, I might be running right now
[Wemmbu] 你居然丢下我跑了，Flame！
YOU LEFT ME, FLAME!
[LettuceK] 我是
I'm
[LettuceK] 正在狂奔
running right now but
[LettuceK] 我开溜了
I'm running right now
[LettuceK] 迟早有你好看的
one day it'll be the other way around
[Wemmbu] 哦，寄了，寄了！
OH, RIP, RIP!
[Wemmbu] 无所谓，兄弟。
don't care bro,
[Wemmbu] 你今天死定了
you're not living to see another day
[LettuceK] 哥们儿，说真的，没人能永远无敌。
just saying man, no one's truly
[LettuceK] 没人能永远称霸。
no one's truly
[LettuceK] 坚不可摧
unbreakable
[Flame] 哟呵呀呵。
Yibbity yabbity.
[Wemmbu] 总算有点共识了。
At least we can agree on something.
[LettuceK] 如果就这样吧..
If that's all..
[LettuceK] 想说的就这些？
If that's all you have to say.
[LettuceK] 若你只能从我这儿带走这些..
If that's all you have to take away from me..
[LettuceK] 我估计没辙了。
I guess there's not much I can do.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟神操作！
BRO MOVE!
[LettuceK] 咱们以后可要常碰面啦。
We're going to be seeing a lot of each other.
[Wemmbu] 嗯。
Yup.
[Wemmbu] 啊。没打中。
Oh. I missed.
[Wemmbu] 哦，行吧。
Oh, okay.
[Flame] 呃...
Uh..
[Flame] 你是..
Are you..
[Wemmbu] 等等！我去追他。
Wait! I can chase him.
[Wemmbu] 我哪来的火箭啊FLAME！
WELL I DON'T HAVE ROCKETS FLAME!
[Wemmbu] 我没有..
I don't have..
[Wemmbu] 哦等等。
Oh wait.
[Wemmbu] 下雨了。
It's raining.
[Wemmbu] 嘿，哥们
Hey, buddy
[Wemmbu] 嘿伙计们
Hey buddies
[Flame] 嘿伙计们
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 但
but
[Wemmbu] 别用重锤
not with the mace
[Wemmbu] 我去 我三叉戟爆了
Oh my a so my Trident broke
[Wemmbu] 我办不到
I can't
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 好的。
[Wemmbu] 我去。
man.
[Wemmbu] 真希望我有烟花火箭
I really wish I had rockets
[Flame] 没地儿打了
oh I'm out of room attack I'm
[Flame] 没地儿了
oh I'm out of room
[Wemmbu] MinX突袭
MinX attack
[Flame] 你傻吗
gonna are you stupid
[Flame] 不你知道是我
no you knew that was me yeah I did
[Wemmbu] 对我知道
[Wemmbu] 我的三叉戟废了
yo my trident broke
[Flame] 我的三叉戟只有五耐久了。
my trident's on five durability
[Flame] 好吧
well
[Flame] 他住哪儿咱门儿清
I mean we know where he lives
[Flame] 你做船吗
do you make a boat
[Wemmbu] 哦对 要不咱直接回
oh yeah wait why don't we just go back to
[Wemmbu] 他家我半根木头都没
his house I don't have any wood
[Flame] 我去我也不懂
oh my god I don't either
[Flame] 快上车
all right get in
[Wemmbu] 来了兄弟
yeah I'm in bro
[Flame] 现在休想动你
Stopping me from killing you right now
[Wemmbu] 你肯定先死我手里
the fact that I'd kill you first
[Flame] 哥们儿你真逗。
You're funny bro,
[Flame] 赢一次就飘了？
you won the one time and you think you're good,
[Flame] 谢了
thank you
[Wemmbu] 好吧，
Well,
[Wemmbu] 我不算厉害，但也没听说你有多强啊。
I don't think I'm good but I mean I haven't heard that you so
[Flame] 好的
Good let me
[Flame] 懂了老天。我全听见了。
Got it God. I heard and I heard it all with that.
[Flame] 就这？就这啊。
Just that that right there.
[Flame] 我压根没听见啊
I mean, I don't even hear that to me
[Wemmbu] 行吧，我咋就摊上这破事儿了
All right, how did I get roped into this
[Flame] 我啥都不知道你问错人啦
I don't know anything you're asking the wrong guy to the on well
[Wemmbu] 这你可问对人了
I'm actually asking the the right guy because you're
[Wemmbu] 其实Lettuce就只盯上了他一个。
actually the only other person the lettuce is hunting
[Flame] 要不咱把XO放这儿？
I mean how about we go XO needs right up here.
[Flame] 好的
All right
[Flame] 等等等等等等，
Wait wait wait wait,
[Flame] 先别急着走。
before you try and go though.
[Flame] 呃，
Uh,
[Flame] 悄悄说句，咱就这么走进去不太妙吧。
lowkey don't think it's a good idea we just try to walk up in here.
[Flame] 好嘞，
Yeah,
[Flame] 刚才卡爆了，感觉
I just got like a massive frame drop so I feel
[Wemmbu] 这地方怕是要挤爆了。
like there's gonna be a million players here.
[Flame] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Flame] 说实话我现在不想打架。
I don't wanna fight right now to be honest.
[Wemmbu] 真没想到你还好这口
I never took you for a
[Wemmbu] 潜行
stealth
[Wemmbu] 潜行老手，鬼祟专家。
guy, a stealth guy, a sneaky guy.
[Flame] 我是说，
I mean,
[Flame] 时候到了也无所谓。
when the time comes it doesn't really matter here.
[Flame] 糟了。
Oh bad.
[Flame] 要是拿到隐身药水，估计得砸了用。
If I get invis I guess I gotta pot it with
[Flame] 你让我分享药水？我可没这习惯。
you but I'm not used to sharing potions.
[Flame] 药水好了 嗯 好了 嗯 咱们要喝药吗
potions all right um all right um are we taking
[Flame] 脱了盔甲，不然咱就废了。
off our armor or we're kind of like
[Wemmbu] 哦，我们只是
oh we're just
[Wemmbu] 全开潜行模式，走起，彻底匿了。
going full incognito all right let's go full incognito
[Wemmbu] 彻底匿了，开整。
[Flame] 哥们儿咱这纯属摸黑往里闯啊
dude we blindly walk in there it's
[Flame] 没意义，反正没人看。
no point of in this because no one over is
[Flame] 旁边还有一个
another right besides like
[Flame] 能量到手
winning my energy
[Wemmbu] 好了，出发
Allright, let go
[Wemmbu] 任务开始
mission start
[Wemmbu] 等不及了，我要开秀。
I'm impatient I'm proing
[Flame] 我去！？
What the!?
[Wemmbu] 这城也太疯了吧，我压根没来过这儿。
What this city's crazy I've never actually like been here.
[Wemmbu] 我算整明白了
I'm now coming to the realization
[Wemmbu] 我都不知道这楼在哪儿
that I don't actually know where this building is
[Wemmbu] 哦，八成是那个巨型
Oh maybe it's the massive
[Wemmbu] 基地正中央的建筑
building in the center of the base
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼
Yeah
[Wemmbu] 有道理
that makes sense
[Wemmbu] 那
What did the
[Wemmbu] 哥们儿这波毫无防备啊
Bro is completely unguarded
[Wemmbu] 我的天
oh my days
[Wemmbu] 嘿兄弟
hey bro
[LettuceK] 他那堆东西用不着
that end of his stuff isn't necessary
[LettuceK] 下次敲门就行
you can just knock next time
[Wemmbu] 哦
oh
[Wemmbu] 是Flame的主意
it was flame's idea
[Wemmbu] 我压根不知道他跑哪去了
I don't really know where he ended up
[Flame] 哥们，你这就能说话了？
Bro, you're already talking?
[Flame] 哦，不用了...
Oh, I don't need to...
[LettuceK] 我
I
[LettuceK] 瞅见你们进门，不过...
saw y'all walking in, but...
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[Wemmbu] 你绝对没看见我进来。
There is no way you saw me walking in.
[Wemmbu] 我是潜行大师。
I'm the master of stealth.
[Flame] 你没看见我。
You didn't see me.
[Flame] 你骗人。
You're a liar.
[LettuceK] 嘿，老兄。
Hey, man.
[LettuceK] 你开心就好。
Look, whatever helps you sleep better.
[LettuceK] 啥
What
[LettuceK] 这下你满意了吧？
does that do for you?
[Wemmbu] 弄死你还不简单。
Yeah, we could kill you.
[Flame] 就是啊 为啥不直接开打
yeah like why why why aren't we killing
[Wemmbu] 他 对哦 等等 咱为啥要这么干
him yeah wait why are we doing that
[Wemmbu] 失手了刚才不算
I missed I didn't mean that time
[Flame] 你打算跑路吗
are you gonna run
[LettuceK] 我命由我
I have my life I mean what
[LettuceK] 要吗
do you want
[Flame] 谁准你走的
who that you can leave
[Flame] 哥们你被完爆了
bro you're getting beat now
[Flame] 等等等等
alright wait wait wait
[Flame] 别走啊
actually don't leave
[LettuceK] 有人要不
somebody want
[Wemmbu] 哥们，把你美西螈交出来
bro I want your axolotls
[Flame] 我想让你停下。
I want you to stop
[Flame] 想搞死我啊
freaking trying to kill me
[Flame] 别抢我的
no don't take my
[LettuceK] 别动我的Cedrics，兄弟
don't take my Cedrics bro
[Wemmbu] 哥们，这都赢你多少回了
bro how many times do I have to beat you bro
[LettuceK] 抱歉
sorry
[LettuceK] 我办公室里正有两个活宝在闹腾呢。
sorry I got Beavis and Butthead in my office right now
[LettuceK] 稍等一下
give me a second
[Flame] 老兄要我揍你几次才够
dude how many times do I have to beat you for
[Flame] 就为了让你一直数着
you to just for you to just keep like how many
[Flame] 要我揍你多少次才够啊
how many times do I have to beat you like do you
[Flame] 让我一个人静静 你一直跟着我干嘛
just leave me alone like you've been following
[Flame] 我转悠半天，回回都把你揍趴下
me around and I've beaten you every single time
[Flame] 你还没发现你根本杀不了我吗
like have you not realized you can't kill me yet
[Flame] 我怎么也被卷进来了
like are we not yeah why am I roped into this now
[Flame] 咱俩没戏是吧
like are we not
[Wemmbu] 我怎么也被卷进来了
yeah why am I roped into this now
[LettuceK] 你炸平整座城市就跟玩儿似的。
also you blow up entire cities just when like they
[LettuceK] 不同意 我绝不会 你 你 削弱
disagree with you I would never you you reduce
[LettuceK] 首都被你夷为平地 第一法则被你践踏
capital city to rubble you reduce the first law
[LettuceK] 为啥大伙都管这叫基地
base why do you think people call this
[LettuceK] 新法基地
the new law base
[Wemmbu] 我没这资格
I have no right
[LettuceK] 是你吗
Is you
[Flame] 我还真记得Lettuce那会儿
I actually do remember witnessing lettuce
[Flame] 碎石散落在沙地石匠铺里。
and the rubble laying down in the sand in the mason.
[Flame] 碎石散落在沙地，就在石匠那儿。
[LettuceK] 好嘞
yeah
[LettuceK] 不过话说回来
yeah but you know what well you
[LettuceK] 可你俩只顾着追来追去
but then while you two were spending all your time chasing each other
[LettuceK] 搞定收工，溜了溜了
I got stuff done and I bounced back
[Flame] 为啥我
okay so why am I
[Flame] 我干啥了
what did I do
[Wemmbu] 小火苗干啥了
yeah what did little flame do
[LettuceK] 你这人真不咋地
you're just a horrible person
[Flame] 我真是个烂人
I'm a horrible person
[Flame] 我这是造了什么孽
What have I done
[Flame] 我干了啥
[Flame] 我干啥了？
generally what have I done?
[Flame] 我改主意了
I'm changing my ways a bit
[LettuceK] 没错，我就知道你得扔出去。
Okay yeah, I knew you had to throw it.
[LettuceK] 千钧一发
Last second
[LettuceK] 你无缘无故杀人就像杀自己一样。
You kill for no reason like you kill you
[Flame] 才不是呢。
that's not true.
[LettuceK] 玩得开心
get enjoyment out of it
[Flame] 才不是呢。
that's not true.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 行吧
well would do not
[LettuceK] 不，你说什么都是为了复仇
No, you claim everything's in the name of vengeance
[LettuceK] 少来，你干啥都说是为了报仇
[LettuceK] 但你二话不说就拔剑。
But you don't hesitate to draw your sword.
[LettuceK] 我不
I don't
[LettuceK] 格杀勿论
kill anybody
[Flame] 他们还想干掉我。
And people would try to kill me.
[Wemmbu] 我们刚干掉了七十人大军，他们可没想放过我
We just killed like an army of 70 people not trying to kill me
[Flame] 这就是防御工事。
That's the defense.
[Flame] 我可没给自己找那些大船
I don't I didn't look for them big boats for me
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 随便你
whatever keeps you keeps you
[LettuceK] 随你便 随你便 那就 那就 那就
whatever keeps you keeps you so when so when so when
[LettuceK] 随你便
whatever keeps you keeps you
[LettuceK] 所以呢所以呢所以呢
so when so when so when
[LettuceK] 你发我的时候，其实是你发我的那会儿
you sent me so when it's actually when you sent me and
[LettuceK] 我的老铁全被这玩意儿干趴了
All my friends to die to one of those
[Flame] 那些时光
How those times
[LettuceK] 那简直毫无亮点
that was anything positive because
[Flame] 我早不是当年那个我了。
I mean I'm a new man now.
[Flame] 我改主意了
I've changed what you want
[Flame] 我得改改了。
...I'm going to have to change.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，
Alright,
[Wemmbu] 说累了都。
I'm kind of bored of talking,
[Wemmbu] 干他。
let's kill him.
[LettuceK] 你干掉我，屁用没有，懂？
You kill me, like, nothing changes, you know?
[LettuceK] 哇，你挂了。
Wow, you're dead.
[Flame] 啊，你凉了。
Oh, you're dead.
[Flame] 这就是关键区别。
That's the big difference.
[Flame] 不不不不。
No, no, no, no.
[LettuceK] 你该知道这里等级森严
You realize there's a whole chain of command,
[LettuceK] 对吧？
right?
[LettuceK] 我要是挂了，就换下一位上。
If I die, the next guy takes over.
[Wemmbu] 为啥要搞层层指挥啊，老兄？
Why is there a chain of command, dude?
[Wemmbu] 咱在MC里。
We're in Minecraft.
[Flame] 哎，他说的还真有点道理。
Oh, he is, he is kind of right.
[Flame] 我确实见过副手……
I do remember meeting the deputy...
[LettuceK] 想顶替我的人多的是。
There's all sorts of people waiting to take over for me.
[LettuceK] 哟，你瞧。
Well, look.
[LettuceK] 变强的方式不止一种。
It's just because there's different ways to be strong.
[LettuceK] 名声才是我的追求。
and for me it's the reputation.
[Flame] 嘿，
Hey,
[Flame] 这咋就拦不住我宰——那宰你呢？
so what- how did this stop me from killing- what about killing you?
[Flame] 我就是搞不懂。
Like, I'm just not understanding.
[LettuceK] 你想，
You wanna,
[LettuceK] 你们要是干掉我，
you guys- if you kill me,
[LettuceK] 你跟几百号人断了联系
you break connections with hundreds and
[LettuceK] 千百文明，无数生灵。
hundreds of people and civilizations.
[LettuceK] 颜值不够。
Wouldn't be good looks.
Oh my god.
[Flame] 我去。
[Flame] 能别玩书了吗——抱歉。
Can you stop playing with books and- sorry.
[LettuceK] 这可不是什么好兆头——
It's not good luck to be-
[Flame] 我跟谁绝交啊？
I break connections with who?
[LettuceK] 你也知道，皇城的那些商人嘛...
You know, Capital City, the merchants...
[Flame] 但没人待见我，因为我总把你们干掉。
But no one likes me because I kill you.
[Flame] 不是，那个——
Like, who's- like-
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 不可能——哪有人抢得这么狠。
No one- no way people rob you that hard.
[LettuceK] 为啥觉得我这么——我这么疯是有原因的——我
Why do you think I'm so- there's a reason I'm so- I
[LettuceK] 这下我当警长可当得心安理得了。
feel so fine about calling myself the sheriff now.
[Flame] 我去。
What the- dude.
[LettuceK] 我—我当时就—
I- I was like-
[LettuceK] 看，
Look,
[LettuceK] 就算宰了我
even if- even if you kill me,
[LettuceK] 江山代有才人出
there's always a new leader,
[LettuceK] 总有援军源源不断。
and there's always just another army waiting.
[LettuceK] 其实呢，
And actually,
[LettuceK] 马上就来一个。
there's one on the way right now,
[LettuceK] 既然我现在
since I'm currently-
[Flame] 哎哟！
OW!
[Flame] 他们杀过来了？
They're on the way now?
[LettuceK] 你几个意思？
What do you mean now?
[LettuceK] 嗯嗯。
Yeah, yeah.
[LettuceK] 那你想干啥？
So what do you want to do?
[LettuceK] 想干架？
You want to fight another army?
[LettuceK] 这个肯定更厉害
And chances are that one- this one's stronger
[LettuceK] 比刚才那帮乌合之众强多了。
than that ragtag crew I brought earlier,
[LettuceK] 呃...
so...
[LettuceK] 哥们儿。
Dude.
[LettuceK] 你想咋地？
What do you want?
[LettuceK] 你想干啥？
[Flame] 行。
Can- okay.
[Wemmbu] 咱能不能就，
Can we just,
[Wemmbu] 老铁，
like- dude,
[Wemmbu] 这帮大军休想得逞——
these armies are never gonna-
[Wemmbu] 搞不懂你为啥觉得这能成
I don't know why you think it's a good idea to try
[Wemmbu] 挑战服务器两大顶尖高手。
and fight the two strongest players on the server.
[Wemmbu] 就像，
Like,
[Wemmbu] 这些小不点约翰大军
these armies of little- little Johns
[Wemmbu] 他们永远拿我们没辙。
are never gonna do anything to us.
[Flame] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Flame] 他们这下可没法连过两关了。
they're not beating one and then two right here.
[Flame] 这也太离谱了吧。
Like, it makes no sense.
[Flame] 搞定，下一个。
One and then, yes.
[LettuceK] 明白。
You got it.
[Wemmbu] 没问题。
Sure.
[LettuceK] 一、二。
One and two.
[LettuceK] 看，
Look,
[LettuceK] 问题是
the- the point- the fact of the matter is,
[LettuceK] 我-我绝不会停手，除非你投降或者沦为阶下囚。
I- I'm not stopping until you submit or become a prisoner.
[LettuceK] 我良心过不去，不能放你走。
In my conscience, I can't let you go.
[Wemmbu] 或者打到没人敢来为止。
Or until you run out of people.
[LettuceK] 得了吧，没戏。
Well, that's not happening.
[Wemmbu] 好吧，你懂的。
Alright, you know what?
[Wemmbu] 我有更好的主意。
I have a better idea.
[LettuceK] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 咱们别浪费大家时间了？
Why don't we just save us all a lot of time?
[LettuceK] 你有啥想法？
What do you have in mind?
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Alright.
[LettuceK] 聊起来。
Talk to me.
[Wemmbu] 哎呦——
Every- oh.
[LettuceK] 放轻松！Flame，
Relax! Flame,
[Wemmbu] 我在想法子让他别再追着咱们打了！
I'm trying to make it so he doesn't hunt us anymore!
[Flame] 行吧行吧。
Fine, fine.
[LettuceK] 我已经很讲道理了。
I'm just trying to be civilized.
[LettuceK] 我的老天。
Gee willikers.
[Wemmbu] 行，咱有话好说。
Yeah, we can be civilized here.
[Wemmbu] 我也摘头盔跟你公平对决。
I'll take off my helmet to match you as well.
[Wemmbu] 你把所有法务部的人都叫来了。
I- you gather all of your law members.
[Wemmbu] 不。
Not,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 20%
20%,
[Wemmbu] 管他军队有多少人。
not whatever percentage the army was.
[Wemmbu] 全体执法人员。
Every single member of law.
[Wemmbu] 开打。
We'll fight.
[Wemmbu] 等把他们全干掉，
And when we kill them all,
[Wemmbu] 你们队里都没人了。
you're completely out of members.
[Wemmbu] 因为咱能加速这场猫鼠游戏。
Because we can expedite this little game of cat and mouse.
[Wemmbu] 明白了吗？
Does that sound good to you?
[LettuceK] 全员到齐？
Every single member?
[Wemmbu] 多少个？
How many?
[Wemmbu] 有多少人叫多少人！
As many people as you need!
[Wemmbu] 他们连条子都没有！
They don't even have members of law!
[Wemmbu] 我不管！统统干掉！
I don't care! We'll kill them all!
[LettuceK] 哇，这条件也太——太顶了吧。
Oh. That's quite- that's quite the offer.
[LettuceK] 呃。
Um.
[Wemmbu] 得了吧 你现在就怂了
Well you come on you're backing down now
[LettuceK] 不，
No,
[LettuceK] 咱们来点刺激的，走着。
we'll make it interesting, yeah.
[LettuceK] 成交。
Deal.
[Wemmbu] 来啊，看我们把他们全干掉。
Come fight us, we'll kill them all,
[Wemmbu] 接着就轮到你了。
and then we'll finally deal with you,
[Wemmbu] 我和Flame想干嘛就干嘛。
and Flame and I can do whatever.
[LettuceK] 行吧。
Fine! Yeah.
[LettuceK] 走着瞧。
We'll see how that goes.
[Flame] 那你只能等死了。
Well, you're gonna just die, so.
[Flame] 看他从哪儿冒出来。
We'll see where he's coming in.
[Flame] 好的现在，
Now,
[Flame] 搞定！
get!
[Wemmbu] 这就去造点飞天火箭
Now I'm going to craft some freaking firework rockets
[Wemmbu] 我真是受够了，这飞行体验也太糟心了。
So I'm tired of not being able to fly properly.
[Wemmbu] 火箭也是接下来这场架的关键。
As well as rockets would be essential for the upcoming fight.
[Wemmbu] 要是Flame和我真要联手
If Flame and I were really gonna be
[Wemmbu] 单挑Lettuce全军
fighting Lettuce's entire army at once,
[Wemmbu] 我们觉得还得再搞点装备。
we figured that we would probably need some more equipment.
[Wemmbu] 嘿，这些东西都还在呢。
Oh, hey, all this stuff is still here.
[Wemmbu] 呃，其实我们该...
Well, actually, we should, um...
[Flame] 能捡点吗？
Can we pick some of this up?
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 搜刮药水去。
let's loot these potions,
[Wemmbu] 这些肯定超赞。
because these will be really good.
[Flame] 哦，这玩意儿怕不是要塌了。
Oh, this stuff might be falling really soon.
[Wemmbu] 咱是不是该...
We should probably...
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
yeah,
[Wemmbu] 等等，
wait,
[Wemmbu] 就
just- just,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 能多快就多快。
cycle it as fast as you can.
[Wemmbu] 这帮人里有的带着潜影贝，
Some of those guys had shulkers,
[Wemmbu] 这就装进去。
so I'm just putting it in,
[Wemmbu] 呃，
uh,
[Wemmbu] 藏在潜影贝里。
in shulkers.
[Wemmbu]金苹果和药水。
Yeah, the Gapple and the potions.
[Wemmbu] 所以，
So,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢
like,
[Wemmbu] 咱不咋想。
we don't- low-key,
[Wemmbu] 这盔甲有点废。
this armor is kinda trash.
[Wemmbu] 这玩意儿能卖钱诶。
Like, we could sell it.
[Flame] 哦，全没了——全在消失。
Oh, it's all- it's all deleting.
[Flame] 不！不，我正想拿金苹果呢！
No! No, I'm trying to get the Gapple.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，别啊，直接切过去就完事了。
Dude, no, just cycle through it.
[Wemmbu] 直接穿过去。
Just cycle through it.
[Wemmbu] 就像，
Like,
[Wemmbu] 捡起就扔，
if you just pick it up and drop it,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 呃，
uh,
[Wemmbu] 这样它就不会消失了。
it'll reset the despawn timer.
[Wemmbu] 我滴老天！兄弟，
Oh my god! Bro,
[Wemmbu] 东西也太多了！他们怎么——这怎么搞啊，
there's so much stuff! How do they- how do they even,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 这些物品全都要造吗？
produce all of these items?
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，
Alright,
[Wemmbu] 东西先放一块儿用。
we're agreeing to pool together our items just for this.
[Flame] 嗯，
Yeah,
[Flame] 你那边留着。
but keep yours on that side,
[Flame] 别把它们搅和了。
so we don't mash them.
[Wemmbu] 得了，得了，得了。
Alright, alright, alright.
[Flame] 你哪来这么多金苹果？
How do you have that much Gapple, Solo?
[Wemmbu] 呃...
Um...
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 我能收拾一下这些。
I could actually organize these,
[Wemmbu] 要么我就偷个懒，不整这麻烦事儿。
or I could just be lazy about it and not do that,
[Wemmbu] 就这么定了。
which is what I think I'm gonna do.
[Wemmbu] 你知道哪有经验吗？
Do you know anywhere we could get XP?
[Wemmbu] 你瞧，
You see,
[Wemmbu] 附魔瓶是PVP最重要的物资。
the most important PvP material is Bottles of Enchanting,
[Wemmbu] 反正能用经验修补
since you can use it with the Mending
[Wemmbu] 修甲附魔。
Enchantment to repair your armor.
[Wemmbu] 真不走运。
Unfortunately,
[Wemmbu] 不过
though,
[Wemmbu] 在不稳定生存服上，
on the Unstable SMP,
[Wemmbu] 没有村民。
there are no villagers,
[Wemmbu] 这是为数不多的入手途径之一，
which is one of the only ways of getting them,
[Wemmbu] 这玩意儿可稀罕了。
so they're incredibly rare.
[Flame] 差点就得手了。
Or I would have.
[Wemmbu] 呃...
Um...
[Wemmbu] 好吧，我有个点子，不过嘛...
Okay, I have an idea, but, uh...
[Wemmbu] 哎，你猜怎么着？
Well, you know what?
[Wemmbu] 就这么干。
We'll just do it.
[Wemmbu] 没事。
It's fine.
[Flame] 咱们要干啥？
What are we about to do?
[Flame] 我寻思这主意不太靠谱
I don't know if- if it's your idea,
[Flame] 这主意可不咋地。
it's probably not a good one.
[Wemmbu] 咱们马上要整点好玩的，
We're about to get up to some,
[Wemmbu] 呃，
uh,
[Wemmbu] 邪恶又热辣的活动。
some evil-hot activities.
[Flame] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 咱这能干啥坏事啊？
What could we possibly be doing that's evil-hot activity?
[Wemmbu] 来我私人语音频道。
Here, join my private voice chat group.
[Wemmbu] 主城就在那儿。
Okay, so there's Capital City.
[Wemmbu] 跟我来。
Uh, come with me.
[Wemmbu] 哦，我看到命名牌了。
Oh, I already see name tags.
[Wemmbu] 这啥情况——好吧。
What even- okay.
[Wemmbu] 走，去黑市。
We're going to the Black Market.
[Flame] 哦。我从没听说过
Oh. I've never- I've never heard of
[Wemmbu] 这我熟。
this before.
[Wemmbu] 嗯，好嘞。
Okay, yeah.
[Wemmbu] 嗯，就在这儿。
Yeah, it's right here.
[Flame] 呃…我这是在看啥？
Um... What am I- what am I looking at?
[Wemmbu] 咱们要洗劫这地方了。
we're about to rob this place,
[Wemmbu] 那咱就不用客气了。
so we don't really need to be courteous.
[Wemmbu] 好，这下应该能开了。
Alright, this should open it.
[Wemmbu] 呃...
Um...
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Alright,
[Wemmbu] 我把他们的绝密破门给拆了。
so I think I broke their super secret and insecure door.
[Wemmbu] 哦。
Oh.
[Wemmbu] 我搞砸了。
I screwed.
[Flame] 人呢-哦，好吧。
Where is- Oh, okay.
[Flame] 好吧，那这是啥——
Okay, so what is-
[Wemmbu] 下来。
Come down.
[Flame] 好嘞，
Okay,
[Flame] 怎么有人困在下面
how- why are there people trapped underneath
[Flame] 他们可能只是在修门。
the- the- they might just be fixing the door,
[Flame] 真心话。
genuinely.
[Flame] 他们就在下面。
They're just down there.
[Wemmbu] 谁知道呢，老铁。
Yeah, who knows, bro?
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Alright,
[Wemmbu] 我有个绝妙计划能搞到海量经验。好了，
I have a genius plan to get us a bunch of XP. Alright,
[Wemmbu] 准备好了。
get ready.
[Flame] 我的老天。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 这走廊咋这么长？
Why is this corridor so long?
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 我去，这啥——我早该——哈？
Yeah, what the- I knew- What?
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[Flame] 你来过这儿多少次了？
How- how many times have you been here?
[Wemmbu] 我还真没来过这儿。
I've actually never been here.
[Wemmbu] 早有耳闻。
I've only heard about this place.
[Wemmbu] 哦，你还蒙在鼓里呢。
Oh. So, I look, you don't even know.
[Flame] 你压根不知道这事。
So you have no idea of this.
[Wemmbu] 我听说有人在卖，
I just know that people sell,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 稀有物品在此。
rare items down here.
[Wemmbu] 但这好像不太合法，我也不是百分百确定。
And it's somehow illegal, but I'm not 100% sure.
[Wemmbu] 跟税有关。
Something to do with taxes.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 看，
look,
[Wemmbu] 他们全都，
they're all,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 交易这些事。
trading and stuff.
[Wemmbu] 真祥和。
How peaceful and calm.
[Flame] 他们有经验值。
They have XP,
[Flame] 我去！
what the-
[Flame] 净瞎扯。
There's a lot made up.
[Wemmbu] 有方块没？
you got any- you got any blocks?
[Wemmbu] 搞到些方块。
Alright, I got some blocks.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Alright.
[Wemmbu] 大伙儿好！
Hello, everyone!
[Wemmbu] 大伙儿注意啦！
Hello! Everyone, attention!
[Wemmbu] 打劫。
This is a robbery.
[Wemmbu] 好的？
Alright?
[Wemmbu] 呃，
Uh,
[Wemmbu] 我看到有人带经验瓶了。
I saw some people with XP. Give- give us all your items.
[Wemmbu] 交——把东西全交出来。
[Wemmbu] 想死是吧？
Do you wanna die?
[Wemmbu] 我本来想打别人来着。
Actually, I was gonna hit someone else.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，
Alright,
[Wemmbu] 排好队，挨个打劫。
everyone get in an orderly line and I'm robbing you all.
[Wemmbu] 你瞧，
You see,
[Wemmbu] 我和Flamefrags是最强玩家
Flamefrags and I are the strongest players,
[Wemmbu] 说到底。
after all.
[Wemmbu] 咱可是人见人怕的主。
So, we're pretty feared by everyone else.
[Flame] 他们居然还排上队了。
No way they're actually lining up.
[Wemmbu] 瞧见没，老铁？
See, bro?
[Wemmbu] 这才是真正的气场。
This is what real aura is.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay,
[Flame] 你这是在——你这是在——你这是在瞎捡——好吧。
you're- you're- you're just picking up- Alright,
[Wemmbu] 好嘞
alright,
[Wemmbu] 好嘞。
alright.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，兄弟。
Alright, you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 你。你。全都是你的。
You. You. All of it.
[Wemmbu] 你的全部经验值。
All your XP.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Alright,
[Wemmbu] 杀鸡儆猴。
we gotta make an example out of someone.
[Wemmbu] 不交经验就这下场。
That's what's gonna happen if you don't give the XP.
[Wemmbu] 瞧，
See,
[Wemmbu] 刚捡的。
you just picked it up.
[Wemmbu] 不，别啊！快上！
No, come on! Come on!
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 有人一直在抢！
Someone- they keep picking it up!
[Wemmbu] 忙活半天就一点经验。
I have one XP from all of that.
[Wemmbu] 不，要死的是你。
No, you're dying.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 这帮人一半连麦都不开。
half these people don't even have voice chat.
[Wemmbu] 就这么回事。
That's why.
[Wemmbu] 你。全归你了。
You. All of it.
[Wemmbu] 全部。
All of it.
[Wemmbu] 全都要。
[Wemmbu] 我们全都要。
We need it all.
[Wemmbu] 一瓶不剩。
Every last bottle.
[Wemmbu] Flame。
Flame.
[Wemmbu] 所以遇到人直接干掉就完事了
This why you just got to like kill people when they
[Wemmbu] 别瞎忙活了。
Stop doing stuff.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay,
[Flame] 你搞死我了！你是我最烦的人！
you're killing me! You were the hate to me!
[Flame] 好的。
Alright.
[Flame] 来啊。
Come on.
[Flame] 我们拖太久了。
We're taking too long.
[Flame] 好的。
Alright.
[Wemmbu] 是是是，你说得都对。
Yeah, you're right.
[Wemmbu] 你太磨叽了。
We look- you are taking too long.
[Wemmbu] 经验。经验。经验。
XP. XP. XP.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
You.
[Wemmbu] 你扔了它。
Drop it.
[Wemmbu] 全都要。
All of it.
[Wemmbu] 你的全部经验。经验。经验。
All of your XP. XP. XP.
[Flame] 谁有经验值，我就爆谁金币。
If I see anyone with XP, they're taking-
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 如果——如果——它——
If- if- it's-
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Flame] 好嘞。
Here.
[Flame] 快丢出来。
Yo, drop it.
[Flame] 扔了它。
Drop it.
[Wemmbu] 你。我盯着你呢。
You. I see you.
[Wemmbu] 你直接扔我身上了！不，兄弟。
You. You just threw it on me! No, bro.
[Wemmbu] 你死定了。
You're dying.
[Flame] 喂，别捡那个。
Yo, drop that.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Buddy.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟！
Buddy!
[Wemmbu] 你。你的全部家当。
You. All your items.
[Flame] 嘿，赶紧的，扔出来。
Yo, drop- drop it.
[Flame] 扔了它。
Drop it.
[Wemmbu] 你。你的全部经验值。
You. All your XP.
[Flame] 嘿，扔了，快扔。
Yo, drop- drop it.
[Flame] 兄弟，真不想干你，哥们。
Bro, I don't wanna kill you, bro.
[Flame] 哦豁。
Oh, oh.
[Flame] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Wemmbu] 他们简直就是在暴殄天物。
They're genuinely just, like, wasting it.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 他们居然学会了。
And they're picking it up.
[Wemmbu] 他们捡起来就浪费了。
They're picking it up and they're wasting it.
[Flame] 你只是在乱杀。
You're just killing.
[Flame] 用不着干掉它们。
You don't need to kill them.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Yes, I do.
[Wemmbu] 他们老乱捡还浪费。
They keep picking them up and wasting it.
[Wemmbu] 他们老实待着就没事。
I wouldn't kill them if they were just listening.
[Flame] 有人有经验吗？
Okay, does- does anyone else have XP?
[Flame] 你的。
Oh, yours.
[Wemmbu] 这人还没死透。
No, this guy still has stuff.
[Wemmbu] 嘿，剩下的都交出来。
Yo, drop- drop the rest.
[Flame] 可你揍的是我啊。
Yeah, but you're punching me.
[Wemmbu] 哟，
Yo,
[Wemmbu] 你打我干嘛。
you're punching me,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟！
bro!
[Flame] 我可不想真宰了谁。
I don't wanna actually kill anyone.
[Wemmbu] 快爆！快——爆装备啊！
Come on! Drop- drop it.
[Wemmbu] 扔了它。
Drop it.
[Wemmbu] 经验全交出来。
Drop your XP. All of it.
[Flame] 全都要。
All of it.
[Flame] 全都归我了。
[Flame] 全都要。
All of it.
[Wemmbu] 哟，我——
Yo, I-
[Wemmbu] 喂，别捡那个。
Yo, drop that.
[Flame] 扔了。
Drop that.
[Wemmbu] 哦，等等。
Oh, wait.
[Wemmbu] 哟，
Yo,
[Wemmbu] 我觉得我被封了。
I think I've banned,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 五个连经验都没有的家伙。经验。
five people who just did not have XP. XP.
[Flame] 还有人吗？
Anyone else?
[Flame] 多谢。
Thank you.
[Wemmbu] 看，
See,
[Wemmbu] 现在他们——不，
now they- no,
[Wemmbu] 这下他们可算听我的了。
now they listen to me,
[Wemmbu] 不过。
though.
[Wemmbu] 谁挡路我锤谁。
If I just kill anyone that even,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 藏经验？
tries hiding XP-
[Wemmbu] 没它掉得慢多了。
They just drop it so much faster without,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 休想反抗。
any resistance.
[Flame] 只是呢，
It's just,
[Flame] 喜欢，
like,
[Flame] 单手用也太不尊重了。
it's a little disrespectful to be offhanding it,
[Flame] 至少。
at least.
[Flame] 不，
No,
[Flame] 逮到你了！
I saw you! I saw you! Just kill them,
[Wemmbu] 快干掉他们！
[Wemmbu] Flame！噢，
Flame! Oh,
[Flame] 好的。
okay.
[Flame] 随便吧。
bro, whatever.
[Flame] 尽量不去想那些打打杀杀的事了。
Trying to put the killing behind me a little bit.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 嗯，
well,
[Wemmbu] 试过了，没啥用。
I tried doing that and it didn't really work out,
[Wemmbu] 那么。
so.
[Wemmbu] 有人有旋风棒吗？
Anyone got breeze rods?
[Wemmbu] 有旋风棒吗？
Any breeze rods?
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这旋风棒的钱我掏了。
Yo, I'll pay for the breeze rods.
[Wemmbu] 我这次真给钱。
I'll actually pay.
[Flame] 嘿，快撒手。
Yo, drop that.
[Flame] 喂，别别别松手。
Yo, okay, don't- don't- drop it.
[Flame] 赶紧的，交出来。
Yo, drop it.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟你图啥呢。
I don't even know why you tried bro.
[Flame] 这家伙——噢，
This guy's- Oh,
[Wemmbu] 这货在打我！兄弟，
this dude's fighting me! Dude,
[Wemmbu] 他连英雄都不是。
he's not even the hero of the village,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
bro.
[Wemmbu] 这波收获不错。
Alright, I'm feeling pretty good about our haul.
[Wemmbu] 我去，他们咋跟过来了？
Yo, why are they following us?
[Flame] 他们要奋起反抗了吗？
Are they about to stand up for themselves?
[Wemmbu] 快跑！快撤！
RUN! Get out!
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Flame] 谢了啊——喂！兄弟，别打我啊。
Thank you for- Oh! Dude, hey, don't hit me, bro.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 还真有，
there actually are,
[Wemmbu] 这附近有都城卫兵。
capital city guards near here,
[Wemmbu] 不过。
though.
[Wemmbu] 咱们该动身了吧。
We should probably- we should probably get going.
[Wemmbu] 赶紧的赶紧的赶紧的。
Let's get- let's get- let's get going.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 走，去商人城。
Let's go to Merchant City.
我们去了Unstable SMP最大的贸易小镇，
We headed to the largest trading town on the Unstable SMP,
商贾城
Merchant City,
有些东西没卖出去
since there are some items that weren't sold in
这仗得靠黑市帮忙。
the black market that we'll need for this fight.
这地方通常戒备森严。
It's usually pretty heavily guarded,
但今天我们简直是大摇大摆就进去了。
but today we were kind of just able to waltz in.
商人城最牛小店，欢迎光临。
Welcome to the finest establishment in all of Merchant City.
[Wemmbu] 嗯 嗯
um um
[Wemmbu] 这玩意儿真带劲
you know what's good
[Wemmbu] 能给我整点吗
yo can I can I get some
[Wemmbu] 有吃的吗
can I get some good eats
[Wemmbu] 这我可吃不了
okay this is I can't eat this
[Flame] 好的
okay
[Flame] 咱们来这儿干嘛？这到底啥情况？
why are we here what even is this
[Wemmbu] 整点好吃的
I guess some good eats
[Wemmbu] 新兴都市头号好去处
the finest establishment of all emergent city
[Flame] 底下怎么有头猪
why is there a pig at the bottom
[Wemmbu] 因为这玩意儿叫热辣野猪
because it's called the hot hog
[Flame] 这哥们儿在这儿坐了多久啊？
so this dude has been sitting here for how long
[Flame] 兄弟们，这玩意儿永远留这儿了。
Bros, it's in here forever.
[Wemmbu] 看吧，所有人都晓得
See, everyone knows that like when you
[Wemmbu] 当你想要点古怪可疑的玩意儿时
when you like need something like strange and suspicious
[Wemmbu] 你坐在酒馆角落里头
you you sit in a tavern in the corner and then
[Wemmbu] 你等着
you just wait
[Flame] 我们认真的吗 为啥不
are we are we serious why don't
[Flame] 我们随便逛逛
we just look around
[Flame] 我肯定行
I'm sure okay
[Wemmbu] 我本想
I wanted to
[Wemmbu] 找个卖下界合金的，不过通常
find someone who sells netherite but it's usually
[Wemmbu] 城里没得卖
not sold in the city
[Wemmbu] 我有个好主意
okay I have a genius idea
[Wemmbu] 怎么搞到我的下界合金这些林地府邸才有
on how to get my netherite so these mansions have
[Wemmbu] 里面都是些超级富豪。
like really rich people in them
[Wemmbu] 好的
okay
[Wemmbu] 嘿兄弟 敲敲门
hey bro knock knock
[Wemmbu] 瞅见名牌了 你在线别装啦
I see your name tag I know you're online
[JustinJeff4son] 嘿兄弟 你们在我家干啥呢
hey bro yeah what are you guys doing at my house
[Wemmbu] 你完蛋了
you're fitted up
[Wemmbu] 嗯对 我来了
um yeah so I'm here
[Wemmbu] 咱俩做个交易。
I propose a trade offer.
[JustinJeff4son] 有品位。
Man of good taste.
[Wemmbu] 嗯
um
[JustinJeff4son] 这市场里就属我最阔。
and I'm the richest in this market
[Wemmbu] 好嘞
all right yeah so could
[Wemmbu] 卖我点下界合金呗，我要四锭。
you sell me some netherite I need uh I need four netherite ingots
[JustinJeff4son] 哟哟 为啥像你这样的家伙
well well why does a guy like
[JustinJeff4son] 你需要下界合金
you need netherite
[Wemmbu] 无所谓
It doesn't matter
[JustinJeff4son] 我是觉得不咋地
I mean I I don't think
[JustinJeff4son] 你要的我也有求
you need it and and I need something
[JustinJeff4son] 没这玩意儿就赶紧撤吧，太值钱了
way more valuable so if you don't have it you can just leave
[Wemmbu] 啥 你要干啥
what what do you
[Wemmbu] 我刚干掉
I just kill
[Wemmbu] 刚宰了
[Wemmbu] 好吧
all right
[Wemmbu] 抱歉
sorry
[JustinJeff4son] 经验修补
mending books
[Wemmbu] 附魔为什么我是说我有我
mending why I mean I have I'm
[Wemmbu] 修甲
mending armor
[Wemmbu] 我这就给你。
here I'll give you I'll give
[Wemmbu] 一整套带经验修补的下界合金盔甲
you a full set of netherite mending armor for
[Wemmbu] 四个下界合金锭 行 行 我 我觉得咱
four netherite ingots okay okay I I think we
[Wemmbu] 四个下界合金锭
four netherite ingots
[JustinJeff4son] 好吧好吧我我寻思咱
okay okay I I think we
[JustinJeff4son] 三人组队
can do a trio
[Wemmbu] 你咋还犹豫上了我不过
well why are you acting hesitant I just
[Wemmbu] 这波你血赚
gave you like the best deal of your life
[JustinJeff4son] 嘿，老兄
Hey man,
[JustinJeff4son] 这屋里我啥都不缺
I have everything I want in this house
[Wemmbu] 好的。
except for mending clearly
[Wemmbu] 引擎到手了吗
Are you got the you got the engine
[Flame] 超赞引擎？
awesome engine?
[Flame] 你下巴都积灰了。
Your chins are dusty.
[JustinJeff4son] 不跟瞧不上我的人打交道
I don't do business of people who diss me
[Flame] 好吧，
Well,
[Flame] 这儿又不是我在做买卖
I'm not the one trading here in my
[JustinJeff4son] 好的
Okay
[JustinJeff4son] 你给我两件盔甲。
You give me you give me two pieces of armor,
[JustinJeff4son] 哦，
oh,
[Wemmbu] 敢骗我你就死定了
I could just kill you if you scam me so
[JustinJeff4son] 说得在理。
You know, that's a good point.
[JustinJeff4son] 合作愉快。
It's a pleasure to do business.
[Flame] 顺便一提，你们的椅子全是垃圾。
And your chairs are trash, by the way.
[Wemmbu] 这玩意儿肯定带劲。
We're going to love that in there.
[Wemmbu] 得嘞，看好这小子。
All right, get this kid.
[Flame] 我需要矿车。
Oh, I need carts.
[Wemmbu] 我要矿车。
I need carts.
我和Flame还缺些东西。
Flame and I still needed a few more items.
好的
Specifically,
我要火药和纸来做烟花火箭。
I needed gunpowder and paper for firework rockets.
所以我拿几套盔甲换了点别的
So I traded a few more of my armor sets
就为这点材料。
for a shelter full of those materials.
我随后绕道去了趟废弃试炼场。
I then made a detour to an abandoned trial chamber
刷了点旋风棒，就为搞些风弹。
and grinded out some breeze rods for wind charges.
然后我回了Flame的基地
and then I headed back to flames base in
备战就绪
order to ready myself for the upcoming battle
[Wemmbu] Flame
Flame
[Wemmbu] 好吧，我只有三个半
okay I only have I have three and a little bit of
[Wemmbu] 经验堆
xp stacks that is
[Flame] 行吧，我这儿还有一大堆呢
okay I have like a lot more but
[Flame] 我这么拼，奖励该多给点吧
I low-key deserve more because I'm on the ground
[Flame] 我用的又不是重锤，当然啦。
and I'm not using a mace and sure
[Wemmbu] 那必须的
so naturally
[Wemmbu] 菜鸟升级更费劲
you know the the weaker player would need more xp
[Flame] 凭实力说话的玩家
I mean naturally the player who plays fair
[Flame] 跟天上飞的那哥们儿一比。
compared to the dude that's flying in the air.
[Wemmbu] 公平是啥意思
What does being fair
[Wemmbu] 这和力气大小有关吗？
have to do with how strong someone is?
[Flame] 因为你压根不是正经
Because you're not a true
[Flame] 战士，这是个
fighter, it's a
[Flame] 老兄
dude
[Wemmbu] 拎着重锤天上飞。
flying in the air with a mace.
[Wemmbu] 我才不在乎当什么正经战士呢。
I don't care about being a true fighter,
[Wemmbu] 我更强了。
I'm stronger.
[Flame] 你不行。
You're not
[Flame] 更猛。
stronger.
[Wemmbu] 我当然是
Well, I clearly am,
[Wemmbu] 因为你正跟我较这个真。
because you're having this debate with me.
[Wemmbu] 强弱无定论。
Strength is subjective.
[Wemmbu] 不，
No,
[Wemmbu] 不是。
it's not.
[Wemmbu] 其实吧
It's actually
[Wemmbu] 最客观的事之一
one of the most objective things
[Wemmbu] 我感觉。
I feel like.
[Flame] 你这实力，拿个重锤都费劲
How strong you are, using a
[Flame] 能秒人的武器
weapon that can one-tap against a dude that's
[Flame] 在地上。
on the ground.
[Wemmbu] 你锻造台呢？
Yeah, where's your smithing table at?
[Flame] 真高手。
What a pro.
[Flame] 应该就在这儿
Think it's in here
[Wemmbu] 你有个经验农场的复制品
You have a dupe an XP farm
[Flame] 我搞了个刷怪塔。
Well, I have a web farm.
[Wemmbu] 我去 升级模板都忘了
Oh my god, I forgot about upgrade templates
[Flame] 你也来点珍珠呗
You join me some pearls
[Flame] 小约翰
The little John-
[Wemmbu] 啥？
what?
[Flame] 珍珠。
pearls.
[Wemmbu] 或者等我一下。
or I give me a sec.
[Flame] 还没
yet
[Flame] 行吧，随便
Okay, whatever
[Wemmbu] 行，装备齐活了。
Alright, I think I'm fully geared.
[Flame] 呃...
Uh...
[Flame] 我再确认一下。
Let me just double check.
[Flame] 我也齐活了。
I think I'm fully geared, too.
[Flame] 我得吃点东西补补饱食度。
I need to eat something for OP saturation.
[Flame] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 开吃。
Let's eat this.
[Wemmbu] 该往哪走？
Where are we supposed to go?
[Wemmbu] 咱们直接冲他们老家？
Are we just going to, like, their base?
[Flame] 呃...
Uh...
[Flame] 他们到哪儿都能找到我们。
I mean, like, they pretty much find us anywhere,
[Flame] 我们肯定能行
I'm sure we could
[Flame] 到哪都逃不过他们的眼睛
probably go anywhere and they'll find us
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Yes,
[Wemmbu] 我可能试过
I might have tried
[Flame] 你选就对了。
You just pick.
[Flame] 嗯哼，
yeah,
[Flame] 咱去他们熟的地儿，我随便挑一个就成。
and we go somewhere that they know so I would just pick somewhere
[Flame] 这就像全场随便玩
That's like get to play overall
[Flame] 窗上落雨
the windows rain
[Flame] 没有空位
No spot
[Flame] 咱这是要去哪儿啊，不如直接去里世界得了，多省心。
Where we going in like why don't we just like ripside it is brain.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Bro,
[Wemmbu] 矿车里还有好多货呢。
because there's so much more or coming in my carts,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟
bro
[Flame] 谁会料到咱们来这手？
Who's gonna see us coming?
[Flame] 说真的，
Realistically,
[Flame] 你觉得这次法律能管多少人？
how many people do you think the law will have?
[Flame] 你让他们把人都叫上。
You told them to bring everyone,
[Flame] 不过话说回来
but like,
[Flame] 这玩意儿啥时候...
when does that...
[Flame] 好吧，
Well,
[Wemmbu] 你基地那边有差不多60人的大军。
they had an army of like 60 at your base,
[Wemmbu] 然后Lettuce说还有一支军队正在路上。
and then Lettuce said there was another army on the way.
[Wemmbu] 估计是，那可能还得再加50。
Probably, so, that'd probably be another 50,
[Wemmbu] 但我们干掉了一个。
but we killed one of them.
[Wemmbu] 大概几百号人吧。
Probably about like a couple hundred people.
[Flame] 懂的都懂。
You know,
[Flame] 要是咱们用激流
if we riptided,
[Flame] 咱们早该到了。
we would probably be there already.
[Wemmbu] 好耶，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 但大军不在。
but the army's not here,
[Wemmbu] 那我们干啥呢？
so what would we be doing?
[Flame] 等着呢？
Waiting?
[Flame] 对，没错。
Yeah, exactly.
[Wemmbu] 尽情享受这美妙时刻...
So just enjoy this beautiful...
[Wemmbu] 老兄，矿车里都能玩皇室战争了。
Dude, you can play Clash Royale in the minecart.
[Flame] 不过这也太低调了吧。
Yeah, but this is low-key.
[Flame] 我们开溜。
We're moving.
[Flame] 边走边打皇室战争更危险。
It's more dangerous to play Clash Royale while I'm moving.
It's more  dangerous to play Clash Royale while I'm moving.
[Flame] 更危险。
More dangerous.
[Flame] 要是前面有个坑咋办，
What if there's a pit,
[Flame] 最后跟个陷阱似的。
like a car trap at the end of this,
[Flame] 然后我们掉进去就挂了？
and then we fall into it and we die?
[Wemmbu] 好吧，
Well,
[Wemmbu] 我盯着呢，
I'm watching out for it,
[Wemmbu] 别慌。
so don't worry,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
bro.
[Flame] 信你才怪。
Yeah, I'm supposed to believe that.
[Flame] 我瞅见个东西
I saw something
[Wemmbu] 是你追着要再打一架。
you're the one who was hunting me down to fight me again,
[Wemmbu] 那个...
so...
[Flame] 这啥意思？
Yeah, what does that mean?
[Wemmbu] 这下你总该服了吧。
That means that I really beat you.
[Wemmbu] 我很满意。
I'm satisfied.
[Wemmbu] 是你非要再跟我打的。
You're the one who wanted to fight me again.
[Flame] 你安全得很。
You're not in any danger.
[Flame] 兄弟，兄弟。
Buddy, bro.
[Flame] 你从头到尾都在躲着我。
You were running from me the whole time.
[Flame] 所以我们才伪造了你的身份。
That's why we faked your identity.
[Wemmbu] 你真当我在乎你啊
You really think I care about you that
[Wemmbu] 躲着不跟你打？
much to dodge a fight against you?
[Flame] 我是说，
I mean,
[Flame] 想当初，
originally,
[Flame] 收拾你的时候
when I beat you,
[Flame] 你满世界找我呢。
you were searching the entire globe for me.
[Flame] 然后你把我家炸了个窟窿。
And then you blew a hole in my base.
[Flame] 你完了，我现在就灭了你
Yeah, I should kill you for that right now
[Flame] 你把我家炸了个窟窿。
You blew a hole in my base.
[Flame] 难怪
That's why-
[Wemmbu] 我稀罕你
I like you could
[Flame] 哦，我当然行，但我不想。
oh I definitely can and I don't
[Flame] 好的
Allright
[Flame] 等忙完这茬咱俩好好比划比划。
Some point when we get done with this we take our little fight.
[Flame] 必须的。
I definitely will.
[Wemmbu] 行，那我再赢你一次
Yeah, I mean I'll beat you again
[Flame] 老实说，要是没带重锤和鞘翅
Be honest right now if you weren't using your mace and your elytra,
[Flame] 这是个用剑的套装
and it was a sword-based kit
[Flame] 我们用的还是那套
and we're using the same exact
[Flame] 背包大比拼
inventory who would win
[Wemmbu] 你八成
you probably
[Flame] 为啥呢
and why is
[Wemmbu] 不过那是因为我们会
that but because we would
[Wemmbu] 啥？
what?
[Flame] 我哪会啊
why would I be
[Flame] 近战
at melee
[Flame] 你算哪块小饼干
all better than you
[Wemmbu] 近战来啊
yeah at melee
[Flame] 所以我比你厉害
so I'm better than you
[Wemmbu] 妥
yeah
[Wemmbu] 近战
at melee
[Flame] 我更强
oh I'm better
[Flame] 好的
okay
[Flame] 算你识货
glad you know
[Flame] 还好你知道得用
glad that you know you have to use
[Flame] 重锤在手，天下我有！
a mace in a in a freaking
[Flame] 神级核弹来干我啊兄弟
god nuke to beat me bro
[Wemmbu] 妥
yeah
[Wemmbu] 这就是我比你强的原因
that's why I'm stronger than you
[Flame] 你不行 这不叫强 这叫菜
you're not strong that doesn't make you strong that makes you trash
[Flame] 你就是个作弊的
that makes you a cheater
[Flame] 兄弟，这算哪门子荣誉啊
bro is this honorable
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这才是关键
bro this is what does that mattered
[Flame] 车陷阱 我还以为 嗯 我 我搞定了
car trap I thought that yeah I I got
[Flame] 我先撤了兄弟
out before you buddy
[Wemmbu] 这啥玩意儿
what even is this
[Wemmbu] 我这是在哪
what what am I in right now
[Wemmbu] 那个
that
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[Flame] 你还好吗？
Are you good?
[Wemmbu] 没事，我挂了但问题不大。
No, I died but it's chill though.
[Wemmbu] 能让我进这个一格洞吗？
Can I get in the 1x1 hole please?
[Flame] 兄弟我刚发现我镐子不在背包里当...
Dude I just realized my pickaxe wasn't in my inventory when I...
[Flame] 兄弟，我要是在玩皇室战争的话，
Dude and if I was playing Clash Royale,
[Flame] 我当场就得交代在这儿。
I would have died right there.
[Wemmbu] 想得美！
No you would not!
[Wemmbu] 这波啊，
This was like,
[Wemmbu] 我都没动键盘居然活下来了。
I didn't even touch my keyboard and I lived.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Flame] 那要是路上有陷阱咋整。
Yeah, but if there was a road trap bro.
[Wemmbu] 行吧，腻了，直接飞。
Okay, I'm bored now, let's just fly.
[Wemmbu] 才没有，我才没呢。
I'm not, I'm not.
[Wemmbu] 哦，我们到了。
Oh, I think we're here.
[Flame] 这鬼地方是哪儿？
Where the heck are we?
[Wemmbu] 哦耶耶耶。
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Flame] 你咋发现的？
How did you find this?
[Flame] 啥？
What?
[Flame] 这波真不赖。
This is actually cool.
[Wemmbu] 这儿老早前好像打过一场大仗。
There was like a battle a really long time ago here or something.
[Flame] 嘿，现在能把末影箱给我不？
Yo, can you give the Ender chest now?
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 我去。
Oh, my God.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 能给我些末影箱吗？
Can I get some Ender chest though?
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 我们觉得Lettuce会自己送上门。
So, we think lettuce will just come to us.
[Flame] 呃。
Um.
[Flame] 他八成安插了眼线
you'll find us he probably has a spy on
[Flame] 我兄弟咋找到我的
me bro who knows like how does he find me
[Wemmbu] 他八成喜欢
he probably does like
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这盔甲显得我头好秃
dude I look so bald in this armor
[Flame] 你头秃了
you look bald
[Flame] 你头真秃。
You look bald.
[Flame] 这啥意思？
What could that mean?
[Flame] 就像，当...
Like, when...
[Flame] 咱们到底要干啥？计划是啥？
What's like the plan going into this like what are we about to do actually
[Wemmbu] 干掉他们
kill them
[Wemmbu] 怎么用
how do
[Flame] 干掉他们，但别太狠。
yeah kill them but like
[Flame] 咋样
how
[Flame] 这有啥技巧吗
like like is there like a strategy
[Flame] 怎么省着点用？
we should do to preserve resources?
[Wemmbu] 嗯，这打法
Yeah, so the strategy
[Wemmbu] 打到他们咽气为止。
is to attack them until they die.
[Flame] 我们可不想
We don't want to
[Flame] 讲究策略...
strategically...
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这就是一群木头桩子。
Dude, it's a bunch of log goons.
[Wemmbu] 咱该咋整？
What strategy do we need?
[Flame] 那资源咋办？
I mean, what about resources?
[Flame] 东西烧太快咋整？
What if we burn through stuff too quick?
[Flame] 我们输定了。
We would just lose.
[Wemmbu] 这你得认，兄弟。
That's on you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 干等吧。
I think we just wait.
[Flame] 不讲策略，
No strategy,
[Flame] 我猜是吧。
I guess.
[Wemmbu] 赢就对了。
Well, the strategy is win.
[Flame] 这战术不太行啊。
Yeah, that's not a very good strategy.
[Flame] 那你为啥拿剑
So why do you get the sword
[Flame] 我能坐这儿不？
and I get to sit right here?
[Wemmbu] 因为我...
Because I...
[Wemmbu] 这我真没辙。
I don't know man.
[Wemmbu] 哦
Oh
[Wemmbu] 我剑都没掏。
I'm not even on the sword.
[Wemmbu] 我该上剑蹭灵气吗？
Should I get on the sword for optimal aura gains?
[Wemmbu] 我直接灌了条水道下去。
Oh, I just put water down the whole thing.
[Flame] 不浪费饱食度还是挺好的。
It's nice still not to waste saturation.
[Wemmbu] 我看到有方块在放。
Uh, I see like blocks getting placed.
[Wemmbu] 没看见啊。
I don't see oh yeah.
[Wemmbu] 已留言
That's a leave message
[Flame] 我啥也没看见啊。
Is this I don't see anything.
[Wemmbu] 我的老天。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 我看一堆人都在渲染它。
I see a bunch of people rendering it.
[Wemmbu] 哦哦哦
Oh oh oh
[Wemmbu] 哦。
Oh.
[Wemmbu] 哟。
Yo.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 看他们砌的这堵墙。
look at the wall of blocks that they placed.
[Wemmbu] 啥情况？
What the?
[Wemmbu] 老兄，这根本就是人墙啊。
Dude, this is just a wall of players.
[Flame] 哇，等等。
Wait, whoa.
[Flame] 哇。
Whoa.
[Wemmbu] 哟。
Yo.
[Wemmbu] 哎哟。
Oh, my.
[Wemmbu] 我去，人也太多了。
Dude, there's so many people.
[Flame] 这阵仗自打黑手党后就没见过。
I haven't seen nothing like this since the Mafia,
[Flame] 兄弟。
bro.
[Flame] 这太离谱了。
This looks crazy.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这服务器快凉透了。
Dude, the server is, like, dying.
[Wemmbu] 卡爆了。
My framerate is dying.
[Wemmbu] 我去。
Oh, my God.
[Flame] 我的老天。
Oh, my goodness.
[Flame] 哦。
Oh.
[Flame] 兄弟，快看这满地材料。
Dude, look at all the blocks.
[Wemmbu] 我滴老天
oh my god
[Wemmbu] 哟
Yo
[Flame] 有啥战术没
um so uh any strategy uh going into the show
[Wemmbu] 赢就完事了，兄弟
Win bro
[Flame] 哇塞，老铁
dude holy bro
[Wemmbu] 哦，是Lettuce啊
oh I see lettuce
[Wemmbu] 瞧他这哥们儿 就他一人有盔甲纹饰
look at him bro he's the only one with trims
[Flame] 我去 人也太多了
dude there's so many people
[Flame] 嗯
um
[Wemmbu] 他们排着队送呢
yo they're like lining up
[Wemmbu] 老兄 他们跟蚂蚁似的
dude they're like ants
[Flame] 你以前见过这玩家吗
um have you ever seen this any players before
[Wemmbu] 别啊兄弟
no bro no
[LettuceK] 我们刚才
W- we performed-
[Wemmbu] 我卡爆了，兄弟。
My frame rate, dude.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀。
Oh, my God.
[Flame] 人扎堆了。
There's just a lot of people in one spot.
[Flame] 他吹号了。
Oh, he blown his horn.
[Wemmbu] 噢，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 他们在开火。
they're shooting.
[Flame] 哟，他们开火了。
Oh, they're shooting.
[Wemmbu] 好吧。
Well.
[Flame] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 行，那就开干吧。
okay. Let's just do it, then.
[Flame] 开干吧。
So I guess the fight started.
[Flame] 我去……
Holy...
[Wemmbu] 往后退点。
Back up, by the way.
[Flame] 往后退。
Back up.
[Flame] 哦。
Oh.
[Wemmbu] 我的老天。
Oh, my goodness.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 所以我觉得没死人。
so I don't think it killed anyone.
[Flame] 我觉得确实如此
I think it definitely did
[Flame] 我觉得是卡了吧
I think it's just lagging
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀
Oh my god
[Wemmbu] 聊天
The chat
[Flame] 我的老天
Oh my goodness
[Flame] 哟
Yo
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 看聊天记录。
read the chat
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 一下死这么多人。
So many people just died.
[Wemmbu] 死亡信息
the death messages
[Wemmbu] 死亡-
The death-
[Flame] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Flame] 服务器从没这么卡过
I've never seen the server lag like this
[Wemmbu] 哟，他们靠爆炸冲上来了。
Yo, they're flying up to us with a blast.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀
Oh my god
[Flame] 我的天！
Oh my goodness!
[Flame] 我去！
Holy!
[Flame] 好的。
Okay,
[Flame] 他们还是
and they still a
[Wemmbu] 我搞到了一大堆。
lot of them that's I got a lot of them alright.
[Wemmbu] 开干吧，兄弟
Let's do it, bro
[Flame] 好嘞
A'right
[Flame] 所以
So
[Flame] 我挨揍了。
I get attacked.
[Flame] 兄弟，Mate跟人干起来了
Oh bro, Mate got into it
[Wemmbu] 全围你那儿了
OH THEY'RE ALL CONGREGATING AROUND YOU
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀
OH MY GOD
[Wemmbu] 我的老天
[Wemmbu] 等等，撑住就行，活着就好。
Wait, just okay just live just survive.
[Wemmbu] 我这就去
I'm going to
[Wemmbu] 要开快照吗？
Should I snap shot?
[Wemmbu] 人真多。
they are so many.
[Wemmbu] 我就俩。
I only have two of them.
[Wemmbu] 我去救他们。
I'm going to save them.
[Wemmbu] 我去，血条蒸发术！
Oh my God, I'm taking a bunch of damage
[Flame] 有啥招都使出来。
any technique going.
[Flame] 哦，这下界合金玩家
Oh, there's netherite people
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这玩意儿也太难搞了吧。
Dude, it's so hard up makes people
[Flame] 人山人海。
So many of them.
[Wemmbu] 我直接狂点就完事儿
Yo, I'm just gonna spam click
[Wemmbu] 我被打爆了
I'm getting demolished
[Wemmbu] 我的老天
Oh my God
[Wemmbu] 听我说
You know what, listen
[Wemmbu] 懂了，你露馅了。
I see, I see you.
[Wemmbu] 狼群尽在我手。
I'm in full my wolves.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，老铁。
Yeah, dude.
[Wemmbu] 你真是把海鸥的牛吹上天了
You do pull the max bullseye
[Wemmbu] 我的老天！
Oh my god!
[Flame] 兄弟，这服务器卡得我头回见。
Dude, I've never seen this server just laggy.
[Flame] 还有人没挺住。
Okay, people are dying still.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 漂亮，漂亮，漂亮。
Nice, nice, nice.
[Wemmbu] 放长线钓大鱼。
Just play the long game.
[Wemmbu] 咱就想...
We just want to...
[Flame] 兄弟，装备够用不
Dude, are you sure we got enough gear
[Flame] 就这？
for this, bro?
[Wemmbu] 走着瞧！
We're going to find out!
[Flame] 但愿狼群正在大开杀戒。
Hopefully the wolves are killing people.
[Wemmbu] 他们快撑不住了。
Okay, they're getting killed.
[Wemmbu] 赶紧奶一口。
Heal like super early,
[Wemmbu] 早点回血，别墨迹。
make sure you heal like super early.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
dude.
[Wemmbu] 老兄这人多得我要是
Dude the crowd is so big that if I just
[Wemmbu] 重锤连点直接砸脸。
spam click while macing it just hits people.
[Flame] 猴哥牛哇。
Yeah, monkey nice.
[Flame] 我要顶不住了，被围殴啊！
I'm in like, I'm getting mauled!
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，兄弟，咱们得
Yeah, dude, okay, we need to
[Wemmbu] 多宰几个。
kill more of them.
[Flame] 这我可从没见过！
I've never seen anything like this!
[Flame] 当真？
Are we serious?
[Flame] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 我受不了了
I can't even,
[Flame] 这下面我打不过。
it's hard for me to fight down here.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 我快不行了，真的。
I can barely, okay.
[Wemmbu] 我去，怪围上来了！
Oh my god, I'm getting mobbed.
[Flame] 但狼群杀疯了。
The wolves are killing tons of people, though.
[Wemmbu] 得嘞，得嘞，得嘞。
Alright, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Wemmbu] 多拉点，多拉点。
Pull more, pull more.
[Wemmbu] 你还有狼吗？
Do you have more wolves?
[Flame] 我只剩，一个了，
I only have, like, one more,
[Flame] 但我有点想留着。
but I kinda wanna save it.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，没问题。
Dude, yeah, okay.
[Wemmbu] 我还是用不了烟花。
I can't even use rockets still.
[Wemmbu] 又宰了几个玩家，卡死了。
We kill some more players, it's lagging.
[Flame] 有必要的话我可以用技能。
I could use arts if need be.
[Wemmbu] 来啊来啊来啊。
Yeah, yeah, do it, do it, do it.
[Wemmbu] 这波AOE不错。
That's good AOE.
[Wemmbu] 我得清静清静。
I need some space, though.
[Wemmbu] 人呢人呢人呢？
Where are you, where are you, where are you?
[Wemmbu] 我给你腾地方。
I'll give you space.
[Flame] 我丢，我丢，我丢丢丢。
I'm, I'm, I'm throwing, I'm throwing.
[Flame] 你也没多难打。
You're not the hard to strike.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 我这就…我这就…
I'm just gonna- I'm just gonna...
[Wemmbu] 这儿有个
There's a-
[Wemmbu] 我感觉自己成了活靶子。
Okay, I think there's a huge horde on me.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Flame] 我只是想——
I'm just trying to-
[Wemmbu] 快出雕像区拉开距离。
Just go- go outside of the statue area to get some space.
[Flame] 是是是，我离得远。
yeah, yeah, I'm far away.
[Wemmbu] 你在哪儿？
Where are you?
[Wemmbu] 我把他们引过去，天呐。
I'll lead them to over to you, oh my god.
[Flame] 不，
No,
no,
[Flame] 不，
[Flame] 我还没准备好，
I'm not ready,
[Wemmbu] 你们守好门。
you guys hold the gate.
[Wemmbu] 我去！
Dude!
[Wemmbu] 老天！我这儿人山人海啊！
Oh my god there's like a million people on me!
[Flame] 呃，我还没准备好。
Uh, I'm not ready.
[Flame] 你得顶住。
You gotta continue to hold.
[Flame] 行吧
Yeah, okay
[Flame] 好了，我准备好了
So, I'm ready
[Wemmbu] 我拿着但是...
I'm holding but...
[Wemmbu] 我滴老天
OH MY GOD
[Flame] 你在天上，想干啥...
You're in the air, what are you...
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，我护甲耐久见底了
Dude, my armor's on HIGH
[Flame] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Flame] 我得修修
I had to mend
[Flame] 好的，兄弟
You have infinite time, bro
[Flame] 直接飞上去
Just fly up
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 那他们就不会追我了。
but then they're not gonna chase me,
[Wemmbu] 问题就在这儿
that's the issue
[Wemmbu] 不下地我浑身难受
If I don't stay on the ground
[Wemmbu] 我能飞了。
Okay I can fly.
[Flame] 哦！
Oh!
[Flame] 我拿到潜影盒啦！
I got my shulker!
[Flame] 啊！
Ah!
[Wemmbu] 干掉他！
Get him!
[Wemmbu] 你个二货！
You idiot!
[Flame] 我必须干掉他。
I gotta kill him,
[Flame] 我得干掉他。
I have to kill him,
[Flame] 我必须干掉他！
I have to kill him!
[Wemmbu] 等等，
Wait,
[Wemmbu] 用户名是啥？
okay where where where where who so username?
[Wemmbu] 好，搞定他了，好。
Okay, you got him, okay,
[Wemmbu] 我看见Lettuce了
I see lettuce
[Wemmbu] 我操作起来了，Lettuce。
I'm cooking lettuce.
[Flame] 好的，我可以开始用矿车炸弹了。
Okay, so I can start carting.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 等等，你在哪？
Wait, where are you?
[Wemmbu] 你在哪？
Where are you?
[Flame] 我在郊区晃悠
I'm like on the outskirts
[Flame] 我在你边上
I'm near you
[Wemmbu] 哪儿？
Where?
[Flame] 这我真没法解释
I don't know how to explain
[Flame] 哎我需要支箭
Oh I need an arrow
[Flame] 我没有
I don't have any
[Wemmbu] 一箭射死
Kill someone with an arrow
[Flame] 好的
Okay
[Flame] 我都不敢上盾了
I'm scared to go on my shield
[Wemmbu] 就是别
Yeah don't
[Wemmbu] 嗯，甭了
Yeah just don't
[Wemmbu] 悠着点。
Just don't
[Wemmbu] 老兄他们全都
Dude they're all like
[Wemmbu] 雕像边聚聚
Congregating around the statue
[Flame] 他们冲我来了
Well they're on me
[Wemmbu] 是啊
Yeah they're
[Wemmbu] 我需要
I need
[Wemmbu] 他们没啥组织性
They're not very like organized
[Wemmbu] 我觉得就是它了
I think that's our
[Wemmbu] 我们可以利用这点
We can use that to our advantage
[Flame] 我只要
I just need
[Flame] 一支箭
an arrow like a single arrow
[Wemmbu] 有些人是这样的。
okay some of them well they had
[Wemmbu] 好的，我需要完成我的第一个。
both okay I need to do my first
[Wemmbu] 要箭吗 我给你弄一支
you want me to get you an arrow I can get you an arrow
[Flame] 嗯哼
uh yeah
[Flame] 你有吗
do you have one
[Wemmbu] 你跑不掉的
I'll get you
[Flame] 你们谁有弓
please one of you have a bow
[Flame] 求你了别射箭
please nope no arrows
[Wemmbu] 哦我看到他们了 他们往那边去了
oh I see them I see them going somewhere
[Wemmbu] 哦，他们都冲过来了
oh I see them all running towards
[Wemmbu] 多半就在你附近
the location it's probably to you no
[Flame] 嗯 必须的
um definitely
[Flame] 看来我没得选，矿车先生。
Guess I don't have a choice, Mr. Cart.
[Wemmbu] 哦，对，是你。
Oh, yep, that's you.
[Wemmbu] 我看见你了。
I see you, I see you.
[Wemmbu] 我来帮你搞定Lettuce。
Here, I'll get lettuce off you.
[Flame] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my God.
[Wemmbu] 好的
All right,
[Wemmbu] 生菜归你了。
lettuce is off you,
lettuce is off you.
[Flame] 酷。
Cool.
[Flame] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Flame] 我还得搞点末影珍珠。
I need more pearls.
[Flame] 有末影珍珠吗？
Do you have pearls?
[Flame] 我燃起来了。
I'm burning.
[Wemmbu] 我这儿有点，
I have some,
[Wemmbu] 但你已经集齐大半了。
but you have most of them,
[Wemmbu] 还记得吗？
remember?
[Flame] 我觉着不对。
I don't think that's true.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 我的天，人也太多了。
Oh my god, there's so many people.
[Flame] 我只要那辆车。
Okay, I just need the car.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 漂亮，漂亮，漂亮，漂亮，漂亮！
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice!
Okay,
[Flame] 好的。
[Flame] 我还得接着干，但车不够用啊。
I have to keep doing that, but I need more cars.
[Flame] 这矿车炸弹操作有点难。
It's kinda hard to cart.
[Wemmbu] 我搁这儿刷怪呢。
I'm just farming them in this-
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈！
Oh my god!
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，绝了！
Dude, it's amazing!
[Wemmbu] 逮到你了。
Oh I see you, I see you, I see you.
[Flame] 他们正自相残杀。
They're all killing each other.
[Wemmbu] 我引了一大波怪朝你那边去了。
Okay, I'm getting a bigger group towards you.
[Wemmbu] 好了，准备就绪。
Alright, get ready.
[Flame] 快照快照快照。
Okay, snapshot snapshot snapshot.
[Wemmbu] 搞定。
Did it.
[Wemmbu] 快溜！
Get outta there.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀。
Oh my God.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 我就在那儿一遍遍刷人头。
I'm just like killing people over and over again,
[Wemmbu] 但这根本没啥用。
but it's just like barely making a dent.
[Wemmbu] 天呐，我的耳朵要聋了！
Oh my God, oh my God, my ears.
[Flame] 太离谱了，连一丁点都没上
It's crazy that not even a fraction are on
[Flame] 这简直难到离谱。
me and it's like absurdly hard to play.
[Wemmbu] 溜了溜了，换个风水宝地。
Okay and this is the part where I run away and get a better location.
[Wemmbu] 等等，你在哪？人呢？
Wait where are you where are you?
[Wemmbu] 要帮忙吗？
Do you need help?
[Wemmbu] 有末影珍珠吗？
Do you have pearls?
[Flame] 我蹲你刀房呢。
I'm in your stab shot hole.
[Flame] 我刚干掉几个人。
Okay I just killed some people.
[Wemmbu] 待着别动，这样挺好。
stay in there, that's probably good.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，我这盔甲也太...
Bro, my armor's so...
[Wemmbu] 我就在这儿慢慢点人头。
I'm just, like, picking people off slowly.
[Flame] 兄弟，我也是啊
Dude, yeah, but, I am too,
[Flame] 但他们把我围住了，兄弟。
but they got me boxed, bro.
[Wemmbu] 他们把你堵住了？
They got you boxed?
[Wemmbu] 需要帮忙吗
Do you need me to
[Wemmbu] 放你自由？
free you?
[Flame] 哦。
Oh.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 生菜，兄弟。
lettuce, bro.
[Wemmbu] 快走开！
Get out of here!
[Wemmbu] 哎呀我去。
Oh, man.
[Flame] 我这处境也太怪了
I'm in such a weird spot
[Wemmbu] 我怎么打不着人
why am I not hitting anyone
[Flame] 人真多啊。
These are so many people.
[Flame] 不止一个。
There's multiple.
[Flame] 这帮人其实不赖。
These guys aren't even bad.
[Flame] 这太折磨了。
This is the worst part.
[Flame] 好的。
Must be 9.
[Flame] 又得修了，老兄。
Yeah, I gotta mend again, dude.
[Wemmbu] 我得修修我的重锤，搞什么鬼？
I gotta mend my MACE, what the?
[Flame] 我末影箱没了。
Oh, I lost my ender chest.
[Wemmbu] 我有9个，你要吗？
Ok, I have 9, do you need-
[Wemmbu] 这个归你了。
Take this one,
[Wemmbu] 拿这个。
take this one,
[Wemmbu] 接招！
take it!
[Flame] 好的。
Ok.
[Wemmbu] 天魂，天魂！
Sky Soul, Sky Soul!
[Wemmbu] 兄弟
Bro
[Wemmbu] 他们居然有传送珍珠！这也太离谱了！
they have freakin' pearls! Like,
[Wemmbu] 他们真回来啦！
they're actually back!
[Flame] 你是要锤那些缠着我的人吗？
Do you just mace the people that are like on me?
[Wemmbu] 我回来了。
Okay, I'm coming back.
I'm coming back.
[Wemmbu] 来了来了！
Coming, bro, coming!
[Wemmbu] 撑住。
Hold out.
[Wemmbu] 我直接动手了。
I'll just hit you.
[Wemmbu] 所以我才不爱跟你一块儿抢重锤，兄弟。
That's why I don't like macing next to you, bro.
[Wemmbu] 哟，哟，哟，逮住他们。
Yo, yo, yo, get them.
[Wemmbu] 接着跑。
Start running again.
[Wemmbu] 他们排成一条线时，我就能用烟花炸飞。
When they're in a line, I can use my fireworks.
[Flame] 他们想干啥？
They're trying to do what?
[Wemmbu] 跑起来，别停。
Like, keep running.
[Wemmbu] 想要我垫个底？
If you want me to base them,
[Wemmbu] 跑路的时候就好办了。
it's easier when you're running away from them,
[Wemmbu] 不像……
not like...
[Flame] 我要顶不住了。
I'm getting mauled, though.
[Wemmbu] 干掉那个下界合金佬。
Pop the netherite guy.
[Wemmbu] 我帧数咋回事？
My frame rate- what the heck?
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 游戏偏偏在这节骨眼上卡死了！
my game just like froze at the worst possible time!
[Flame] 我得去会会那些下界合金佬——
There's netherite people who I'll need to-
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 遍地都是下界合金佬。
there's just netherite people everywhere,
[Wemmbu] 真没法儿扯谎。
I can't even lie.
[Wemmbu] 我干掉那个下界合金佬了！穿下界合金的会掉经验！
I dropped the netherite guy! The netherite guys have XP!
[Wemmbu] 下界合金-分你一堆经验！
The Netherite- split your stack of XP!
[Wemmbu] 他们在抢你的潜影盒，搞什么——
They're looting your shulker, what the-
[Flame] 我的潜影盒呢？我压根没潜影盒啊。
My shulker, I don't have shulker.
[Wemmbu] 有人放了个红潜影盒！
Yeah, someone just placed a red shulker!
[Wemmbu] 不是，这啥玩意儿？
Wait, what the-
[Wemmbu] 哟，
Yo,
[Wemmbu] 有人抄着重锤！刚有个倒霉蛋被砸扁了！
someone has a mace! Someone just got smashed!
[Wemmbu] 快看聊天框！
Dude look in chat!
[Wemmbu] 他们哪来的重锤？！
How do they have a mace?!
[Flame] 懂了！
I see!
[Wemmbu] 我溜了。
I'm going to a safe spot,
[Wemmbu] 我在疯狂补货。
I'm hitting a hard restock,
[Wemmbu] 撑住别死。
just stay alive.
[Wemmbu] 老兄这人进我身了！
Dude this guy's in me!
[Wemmbu] 这咋整的？！
Like, how?!
[Wemmbu] 我喝点药水就去宰了他。
I need to re-pot then I'll kill him.
[Wemmbu] 哦
Oh
[Wemmbu] 好家伙，全队都到齐了。
man, the entire army's here now.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，来瓶力量药水。
Dude, I need a strength potion.
[Wemmbu] 这帮家伙掉了啥
what are these guys got drop us
[Flame] 你懂我 我现在感觉
You know I'm just getting like
[Flame] 像样
like shape
[Wemmbu] 取悦我
please me string
[Wemmbu] 你懂的
you know they
[Wemmbu] 万事皆备于我
just think of everything surely I have
[Wemmbu] 绕圈拉弦 对咯 就是这样
a string circle right oh yeah you have
[Wemmbu] 行吧 我来找神装 咱们有这些了
those okay I looking for God we got these
[Flame] 我正挨个点名呢
I'm picking them off maybe it's
[Flame] 我在地上，有点慌，低调低调。
I'm on the ground that I'm a little on the edges is like low key
[Flame] 我在怪物堆里啥也没干。
I in the mob do this nothing.
[Wemmbu] 不，我这是自讨苦吃
No, I'm putting to me see there
[Wemmbu] 不，我自己亲眼看看。
No,I'm putting to me see there
[Wemmbu] 他躲在巨人大军里不敢出来，笑死
Don't do he's hiding inside of the giant army like oh my god
[Flame] 我没经验
I've no XP
[Wemmbu] 哦
Oh
[Flame] 好多人来找我
I'm getting a approach by a lot of people
[Wemmbu] 你在哪儿？
Where are you right?
[Wemmbu] 我给你备了套盔甲。
I'll give you a spare armor set.
[Wemmbu] 咱们碰头就行
We just need to meet up
[Flame] 嗯，
Um,
[Flame] 我在雕像区。
I'm in the statue area.
[Wemmbu] 好的，试试看。
Okay, try it.
[Wemmbu] 哦，老哥，这下寄了。
Oh, dude, it's so cooked.
[Wemmbu] 这简直，像被洗劫了。
It's so, like, raped.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 我看见你了。
I see you,
[Wemmbu] 但我没法让你搭便车了。
but I'm not gonna be able to drop you.
[Wemmbu] 漂亮，漂亮，漂亮！
Nice, nice, nice!
[Wemmbu] 交给我了，兄弟。
I got you, bro.
[Flame] 这帮家伙有人揣着末影珍珠。
Some of these guys have pearls.
[Wemmbu] 确实。
Yeah, they do.
[Flame] 干掉这家伙。
Kill this guy.
[Flame] 逮到他没？
Got him?
[Flame] 漂亮。
Yeah, nice.
[Wemmbu] 珍珠往上飞，再高点，再高点，再高点。
Pearl up higher, higher, higher, higher.
[Flame] 方块在手。
I have my blocks.
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[Wemmbu] 你哪来的方块？
What do you mean you have blocks?
[Wemmbu] 我刚干掉一个家伙，他装备多得能开军火库。
I just dropped a guy with like a million sets of gear.
[Wemmbu] 啊，全给他们捡着了。
Aw, and they all picked it up.
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 我看见他了。
I see him.
[Wemmbu] 不错，不错，真不错。
Nice, nice, nice.
[Wemmbu] 哦。
Oh.
[Flame] 我的错。
My bad.
[Flame] 我挪个地儿。
I'm gonna move.
[Flame] 稍微整点活。
Okay, cooking a little bit.
[Wemmbu] 哎，对对对。
Yeah, yeah.
[Flame] 说真的，他真是个灵魂人物。
Honestly, he's a spirit.
[Flame] 稍等片刻。
Cooking a bit.
[Flame] 哟，我还真有两下子。
Oh, I'm actually cooking.
[Wemmbu] 我跟你一起。
I'm with you.
[Wemmbu] 全宰了。
Just kill all these guys.
[Flame] 我去，我头盔呢，兄弟。
Oh, my helmet, bro.
[Flame] 我的头盔，兄弟。
My helmet, bro.
[Flame] 真逗。
It's all funny.
[Wemmbu] 赶紧走人。
Okay, just get out.
[Wemmbu] 爬到雕像顶上
Get on top of the statue
[Wemmbu] 这就把你的盔甲给你。
and I'll give you your armor.
[Flame] 漂亮。
Nice.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 我可不想把这玩意儿丢这儿。
Yeah, I just don't want to drop it here.
[Wemmbu] 你有末影珍珠吗？
You have pearls?
[Wemmbu] 你彻底出局了？
Are you fully out?
[Flame] 我没方块。
I don't have blocks.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Wemmbu] 我搞不懂你。
I can't get you.
[Wemmbu] 我有一组方块。
Okay, I have a stack of blocks.
[Wemmbu] 一招秒你。
I'll drop you ones.
[Wemmbu] 这儿，就这儿。
Here, right up here.
[Wemmbu] 珍珠直冲我而来。
Pearl right up to me.
[Wemmbu] 好的。你懂?
You get it?
[Flame] 不，
No,
[Flame] 不不不不。
no, no, no, no.
[Wemmbu] 肯定有人捡到了。
Okay, someone must have got it.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Wemmbu] 有镐子吗？
Do you have a pick?
[Wemmbu] 挖就完事儿了，挖就完事儿了，挖就完事儿了。
Just like mine in, mine in, mine in.
[Flame] 我啥也没有。
I don't have nothing.
[Flame] 爆了那个没戴头盔的。
Drop the guy with no helmet on.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Flame] 我头盔都没一个。
I have no freaking helmet.
[Wemmbu] 赶紧离开这憋屈地儿
Just get out of this confined like
[Wemmbu] 我去引开他们，你趁机开溜。
area and then I'll keep you distracted.
[Flame] 老兄，我尽力了。
Dude, I'm trying.
[Flame] 哪儿哪儿都是人。
There's so many people like everywhere I look.
[Wemmbu] 糟了，这位置太要命了。
Oh, I am in a bad spot.
[Flame] 哦，
Oh,
[Flame] 这下可难办了。
I'm in a bad spot.
[Wemmbu] 这儿可不是干架的地儿。
Yeah, we can't be fighting in here.
[Wemmbu] 快走开。
Get out of here.
[Wemmbu] 只是…
Just...
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，你得赶紧撤。
Yeah, you just gotta get out, bro.
[Flame] 兄弟，我随手一扔遍地开花
Dude, everywhere I throw I find
[Flame] 我又回到这老地方了。
myself back in the same spot.
[Flame] 干掉玩家。
Killing people.
[Flame] 我是
I'm
[Flame] 还在乱杀
still murdering
[Flame] 兄弟们，我溜不掉了。
people, I can't get away.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 我还以为你要动手呢。
Oh, I thought you were gonna do that.
[Flame] 啥情况？
What the?
[Flame] 好的！
Okay!
[Wemmbu] 我在重锤里，无敌。
I'm in the impenetrable mace right now.
[Wemmbu] 我溜了。
Okay, I'm out.
[Wemmbu] 他们把我关起来了！
They blocked me in!
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Flame] 兄弟，我简直了...
Dude, I'm just like...
[Flame] 我光着头大开杀戒了。
I'm going on a killing spree with no helmet on.
[Flame] 哦耶，又搞定一个。
Oh, yeah, another one.
[Wemmbu] 我嗝屁了。
I popped.
[Flame] 我去！
Oh!
[Flame] 兄弟，我就是他们
brother I am they
[Flame] 他们一直追着我打，我根本跑不掉。
were like rolling on me so I can't fully get away all there's
[Flame] 都跟我上 等等 怎么这么多人
like everyone on me wait there's so what
[Flame] 都跟我上
like everyone on me
[Wemmbu] 等等，这什么情况？
wait there's so what
[Wemmbu] 这把稳了
we're actually so winning this stuff
[Flame] 我不需要 我不懂 不要 不要
I need no I don't know no no
[Wemmbu] 不不不不不 糟了兄弟 我没看见你在哪
no no no no no oh no man I didn't see where you were
[Wemmbu] 来了来了
here, coming, coming
[Flame] 我需要那个
I need the-
[Wemmbu] 多扔点
just throw more
[Wemmbu] 专业 专业 专业
pro pro pro
[Wemmbu] 我可不—
I don't-
[Flame] 我起不来了
I can't get up
[Flame] 别让他们冲上来！
Don't wincharges them!
[Flame] 干掉他们！
Get em!
[Wemmbu] 你在哪？！人太多没法扔东西
Where are you?! I can't drop you items there are too many people
[Wemmbu] 哦豁
Oh yeah
[Wemmbu] 我懂你意思，
I see what's gonna happen,
[Wemmbu] 来了。
coming,
[Wemmbu] 来了来了
coming, coming
[Wemmbu] 温沙德
Winsharded,
[Wemmbu] 我扔的胜利碎片珍珠
winsharded pearls I dropped them
[Wemmbu] 搞定
Get it
[Flame] 好的
Okay
[Wemmbu] 珍珠退场。
Pearl out,
[Wemmbu] 珍珠就狂扔珍珠。
pearl just spam pearl,
[Wemmbu] 狂扔末影珍珠
just spam pearl
[Flame] 好嘞
Alright
[Flame] 是你搁那儿飞吗？
Is that you flying over there?
[Wemmbu] 好好好好好
Yes yes yes yes yes
[Wemmbu] 珍珠再来一次。
Pearl one more time,
[Wemmbu] 再来一次。
one more time,
[Wemmbu] 再来一个。
one more,
[Wemmbu] 再来一把
one more one more
[Flame] 好嘞好嘞好嘞好嘞
Okay okay okay okay
[Wemmbu] 哟哟 快看这些宝箱 宝箱
Alright, yo yo look in these shulker shulker
[Flame] 好吧…
Okay...
[Flame] 快快快，快捡起来，快捡起来。
Quick, quick, head in, pick it up, pick it up.
[Wemmbu] 啊哈哈 咿呀呀。
Ah-ha-ha hiyayay.
[Flame] 他们在这儿！
Their right here!
[Flame] 那我走？
How about I'm off ?
[Flame] 搞什么鬼！
[Wemmbu] 你好像在我胳膊上迷路了。
okay, I look you lost on my arm
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Flame] 这人有了。
I got it this one guy got it.
[Wemmbu] 不，
No,
[Wemmbu] 我
I
[Wemmbu] 有人得手了。
Someone got something.
[Wemmbu] 有人缺了件护甲。
Yeah someone got something we're out of like one armor piece.
[Wemmbu] 我觉得
I think
[Wemmbu] 我这就回去继续砍人
I'm gonna go back just killing people
[Wemmbu] 怎么耽搁这么久
Actually why I did take a longer here
[Wemmbu] 我先得好好补给一下，然后再行动。
I need to hit a longer restock first and then I'm gonna go
[Wemmbu] 绕到后面 往那边去
back to people just wrap around back towards the towards that
[Wemmbu] 有个老兄在独自耍帅。
There's this one dude, aura farming alone.
[Wemmbu] 我去，他有经验！
Oh my god, he had XP!
[Wemmbu] 我去，这家伙挂机还带着经验。
Oh my god, this guy was just AFK and he had XP.
[Wemmbu] 求求了。
Please.
[Wemmbu] 我干了件蠢事。
I just did something really stupid,
[Wemmbu] 不过没事。
but it's fine.
[Wemmbu] 我把他的图腾拿回来了，没事了。
I got his totem back, so it's fine.
[Flame] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Flame] 我可能还得再来点。
I might need some more.
[Wemmbu] 经验交出来！
Give me the XP!
[Wemmbu] 我去，别啊！
Dude, no!
[Wemmbu] 经验全被他们抢了！
They got all the XP!
[Wemmbu] 我刚拿到重锤！
I just got the mace!
[Wemmbu] 快放我出去！
AHH GET ME OUTTA HERE!
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
OK!
[Wemmbu] 有人用重锤砸我！
Someone just hit me with the mace!
[Wemmbu] 太棒了！
YES!
[Wemmbu] 我拿到重锤了！
I got the mace!
[Wemmbu] 我去！
WHAT THE?
[Wemmbu] 哟 瞧啊
YO THERE'S-
[Wemmbu] 我去 有人带着鞘翅翅来抓我了！
YO THERE'S PEOPLE WITH ELITRA'S ON ME!
[Flame] 他们也有鞘翅？
They have elitras too?
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 有人真在追移动中的鞘翅。
there's someone genuinely chase moving Elytra right now.
[Wemmbu] 这谁顶得住啊？
What am I even meant to do against this?
[Flame] 兄弟，还手啊，这简直——
Dude, fight him back, this is like-
[Wemmbu] 我去，他——
Dude, he-
[Flame] 来啊
Come on-
[Wemmbu] 好嘞好嘞，
Ok ok,
[Wemmbu] 我这就干掉他。
well I'm killing him,
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
yeah,
[Wemmbu] 但用鞘翅杀人有点难。
but it's a little hard to kill someone using Elytra.
[Wemmbu] 没事，我刚把他干掉了。
Nevermind, I just popped him.
[Wemmbu] 他还有把重锤。
He has a mace also,
[Wemmbu] 他想用鞘翅重锤阴我。
he's trying to Elytra mace me.
[Wemmbu] 想得美，这可是我的绝活，懂？
Nah, that's my thing buddy, what?
[Wemmbu] 我太菜了。
I'm so trash.
[Wemmbu] 我差点就干掉他了。
I could have killed him.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
Yes!
[Wemmbu] 逮到他了！
I got him!
[Wemmbu] 我的老天。
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 想要鞘翅吗？我这有多的。
Wait, I got you an Elytra if you want one.
[Wemmbu] 想要不？
You want it?
[Flame] 就这一次。
I just need it this once.
Just one time.
[Wemmbu] 就在那顶上。
Yeah, on top of the thing.
[Wemmbu] 这鞘翅到手了。
Yeah, I got this pair of Elytra.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 我钻地洞了。
I'm in a mole hole.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 没空搜刮了。
Okay, I don't have time to loot this.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，给你个石匠鞘翅。
I'll give you a mason Elytra, bro.
[Flame] 全给我，全给我，全给我。
Give me all, give me all, give me all.
[Flame] 这不太公平。
It's not really fair.
[Wemmbu] 谁在乎啊？
Dude, who cares?
[Wemmbu] 上千个V2在追杀我们。
There are a thousand V2-ing us.
[Wemmbu] 我看见你了，看见你了，看见你了。
I see you, I see you, I see you.
[Wemmbu] 上楼梯。
Come up the staircase.
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 我就想玩会儿……
I was just gonna play some...
[Wemmbu] 好了好了，快去玩会儿...
Alright, alright, go play some...
[Wemmbu] 我扔了鞘翅和重锤……
Here, I dropped Elytra, Mace...
[Wemmbu] 呃…拿火箭。
Umm... Pick the rockets.
[Flame] 哦，
Oh,
[Flame] 我挨锤了。
I'm getting maced.
[Flame] 开溜咯。
gotta fly away.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 这儿有
there's,
[Wemmbu] 喜欢，
like,
[Wemmbu] 这里的鞘翅高手们。
other Elytra macer in here.
[Flame] 就像，
Like,
[Flame] 好久不见...
it's been so long...
[Flame] 等等，有人想用鞘翅加重锤阴我。
Hold on, some dude is trying to Elytra mace me.
[Flame] 我该咋办？
What do I do?
[Wemmbu] 飞走躲开就完事了。
Just fly away and dodge,
[Wemmbu] 然后给他们来一发风弹重锤。
and then Wind Charge Mace them.
[Wemmbu] 我去搞鞘翅重锤哥。
Here, I'll try and get the Elytra maces.
[Flame] 他们全冲我来了。
Yeah, they're just on me.
[Wemmbu] 我是
I'm
[Wemmbu] 来了来了来了。
here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
[Wemmbu] 来了来了来了来了。
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
[Wemmbu] 快溜快溜。
Just fly away, fly away.
[Wemmbu] 揍他？
Hit him?
[Wemmbu] 刚换上复活图腾。
Just offhand totem.
[Flame] 我没有。
I don't have one.
[Wemmbu] 好家伙。
Bruh.
[Wemmbu] 我去，他半空给我秒了。
Oh my god, he just popped me midair.
[Wemmbu] 我去，这家伙有点东西啊？
Yo, why is this guy actually kind of good?
[Flame] 卧槽，兄弟。
Holy, bro.
[Wemmbu] 我去，搞啥呢？
Dude, what the?
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Wemmbu] 这人简直了...
this guy's like...
[Flame] 我滴妈呀
oh my god
[Flame] 我真不想利用这姑娘 该咋办啊
I hate using this girl like what am I supposed to do
[Wemmbu] 兄弟我真心
dude I'm actually
[Wemmbu] 尝尝我的厉害
learning what it feels like to fight me right now
[Wemmbu] 我就这么干
so I do it
[Wemmbu] 我去
Oh god
[Wemmbu] 好嘞，
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 我一直在山洞里修炼
I've been I've learned in a cave
[Flame] 人多势众就以为我不知情吗
If you are a lot do you think I don't know I'm
[Wemmbu] 你死定了
gonna want a lot of you are dead
[Wemmbu] 说一大堆。
just say a lot
[Wemmbu] 天呐 他们在挖我脚下方块！
Oh my god people are digging on me.
[Wemmbu] 我得赶紧溜。
Oh, I gotta get out of here.
[Wemmbu] 这可不太妙
This is not good
[Wemmbu] 我去，不是吧。
Oh my god, oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 我滴妈呀
Oh my god
[Wemmbu] 快救我出洞
Yo, get me out of this cave
[Flame] 他想靠传送翻盘？
He was trying to teleport in for his last wish?
[Wemmbu] 嚯！
Huh!
[Flame] 我的盔甲快撑不住了。
Oh, my armor's so fraught.
[Wemmbu] 我去！天呐，他们杀过来了！
Dude! Oh, my God, they're coming!
[Wemmbu] 兄弟！行吧，
Dude! Okay,
[Wemmbu] 我倒是想揍他，但这货根本打不着啊！
I would fight this guy but I just freaking can't!
[Flame] 你到雕像顶了，我——
You come to the top of the statue, I'm-
[Flame] 我可不—
I don't-
[Wemmbu] 雕像顶上见。
Meet me at the top of the statue.
[Wemmbu] 我身上要装个鞘翅增幅器。
There's going to be an elytra maser on me though.
[Flame] 天啊，Lettuce居然阴我！
Oh my god, lettuce is blue on me!
[Wemmbu] 雕像就在眼前，
Coming to the statue,
[Wemmbu] 雕像顶上见。
coming top of the statue right now.
[Wemmbu] 装备时间不多了。
We're not going to have much time to gear.
[Wemmbu] 准备好咯。
So be ready.
[Flame] 噢，Lettuce在蹲点
Oh, lettuce is camping
[Flame] 我在这儿上头呢。
me up here.
[Wemmbu] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Flame] 冲，冲，冲，冲，冲。
Go, go, go, go, go.
[Flame] 让我——我得——我得再用一次末影箱。
Can you- I need- I just need to ender chest again.
[Flame] 过来。
Come over.
[Flame] 好的，咱们走起！
Go.
[Flame] 卧槽。
Holy bro.
[Wemmbu] 小心，有鞘翅杀手。
Be careful, be careful, there's an elytra maser.
[Wemmbu] 他们马上就到，小心点。
So they're going to pull up, just be careful.
[Flame] 隐身会不会很坑？
Would it be bad to invis?
[Wemmbu] 来嘛 试试看 你瞧 这不就
in uh right do it just try it we look you got
[Wemmbu] 这让我想起了黑帮时代。
to do anything it goes back to the mafia days
[Wemmbu] 呃 其实我是 你需要啥 你干啥的
uh I'm actually what do you need what do you do
[Flame] 棋靴速查
chess playing boots quick check all right
[Wemmbu] 这儿有靴子
boots here
[Wemmbu] 行我还剩点经验快好了
okay I still got some xp I'm almost ready
[Wemmbu] 确实 确实
yeah they're completely they're completely
[Wemmbu] 懵了 天哪我们居然
confused oh my god we actually just
[Wemmbu] 成功脱身 咱们来个了断
got away all right let's finish this
[Flame] 这人也太多了吧
Do there's so many
[Wemmbu] 又一个
another it
[Wemmbu] 快溜吧，老兄！
Better run, buddy!
[Wemmbu] 更好的－
Better
[Flame] 这儿还有别人用重锤吗？
Are there other macers in here?
[Wemmbu] 我敢说肯定还有俩——
I'm pretty sure there's still two-
[Flame] 这咋打？
What am I supposed to do against him?
[Wemmbu] 哦，
Oh,
[Wemmbu] 我没事。
I'm- okay,
[Wemmbu] Lettuce直接黏上他了。
so Lettuce just completely on him.
[Wemmbu] 哎呀，这下可玩砸了。
Oh, you know, this was not the move.
[Wemmbu] 我看见你了。
I see you.
[Wemmbu] 我看见你了。先干掉那个重锤。
I see you. Pop the mace guy.
[Wemmbu] 锤了那个玩重锤的。
Pop the mace guy.
[Flame] 我去。
Oh, my God.
[Flame] 力量 1。
Strength 1.
[Flame] 你居然用重锤砸我。
You just freaking maced me.
[Flame] 你想弄死我？
Are you trying to kill me?
[Wemmbu] 没骑你身上。
No, I'm not on you.
[Wemmbu] 我骑的不是你。
I'm not on you.
[Wemmbu] 我在锤别人。
I'm macing someone else.
[Flame] 我连影儿都没有
I'm nowhere
[Wemmbu] 就在你附近。
near you.
[Wemmbu] 我正跟另一个重锤玩家对打。
I'm fighting another mace user.
[Wemmbu] 有多少重锤玩家？
How many mace users are there?
[Flame] 东西不少。
There's a lot.
[Wemmbu] 哦豁，
Oh yeah,
[Wemmbu] 我刚看见鞘翅重锤哥了，来帮我一把。
I just saw an Elytra Mace help find me.
[Wemmbu] 我滴老天鹅！
OH MY GOD I-
[Flame] 这家伙，等等，
This guy's, wait,
[Flame] 这帮家伙有矿车，他们有矿车。
These guys have carts, they have carts.
[Flame] 哦豁...
Oh yeah...
[Wemmbu] 哦，是矿车爆破小子。
Oh, this is the cart guy.
[Wemmbu] 好吧，我就想——
okay, I just wanna-
[Wemmbu] 玩矿车的都穿下界合金裤。
The cart guys have netherite pants.
[Flame] 看。
Look.
[Wemmbu] 我去
OH MY GOD DUDE
[Wemmbu] 我去，这吓我一跳，天呐。
Dude that jump scared me, oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 我们得——好嘞
We need to- ok,
[Wemmbu] 怎么干掉这个鞘翅重锤哥？
how do we take out this Elytra Mace dude?
[Flame] 去山洞里逛逛？
Uh, maybe go on a cave?
[Wemmbu] 我试过了，但他压根没上钩。
I tried that but he didn't- he didn't like take the bait or anything.
[Wemmbu] 哦。
Oh.
[Wemmbu] 我的鞘翅重锤没了。
Okay I lost the Elytra Mace.
[Wemmbu] 小心点，他可能盯上你了。
He might be on you so be careful.
[Wemmbu] 我就想点掉那几个推矿车的和下界合金玩家。
I'm just trying to pick off the carters and the netherite players,
[Wemmbu] 跟高价值目标似的。
like the high value targets.
[Wemmbu] 这哥们儿正写告示牌呢。
This dude was writing a sign.
[Wemmbu] 啥情况？
What the?
[Wemmbu] 这家伙直接在我眼前秒下线了。
This guy just like logged off in front of me.
[Wemmbu] 哦，他卡了。
Oh, he's lagging.
[Wemmbu] 就是这么回事。
That's why.
[Wemmbu] 我砸不动他。
I can't mace him.
[Wemmbu] 他太卡了。
He's too laggy.
[Flame] 逮到他了。
Got him.
[Flame] 我要被矿车炸到了。
I'm going to get carted.
[Wemmbu] 我要被矿车炸到了。
[Wemmbu] 想得美。
Nope.
[Wemmbu] 我去不了了。
I'm not going to be there.
[Wemmbu] 鞘翅重锤哥在我这儿。
Oh, the Elytra Mace is on me.
[Flame] 这身下界合金套也太神了
Holy the full nether I got on this though
[Wemmbu] 我只是在疯狂杀敌，
I'm just trying to kill as many people as I can while
[Wemmbu] 同时防着对方的鞘翅重锤。
keeping like the Elytra Mace from Elytra Mace me
[Wemmbu] 我得先专注干掉他们那个主力。
I'm strictly Elytra Mace to kill his own guy.
[Flame] 噢，我拿到鞘翅重锤了。
Oh, I'm getting Elytra Mace.
[Flame] 这人必须死。
This guy needs to die.
[Wemmbu] 那咋弄死他？
Yeah, I know, but how do we kill him?
[Wemmbu] 不，
No,
[Wemmbu] 因为他总是一溜烟就飞没影了
because he just flies away whenever
[Wemmbu] 我像揍你一样拿重锤砸他。
I try and Mace him like I do to you.
[Flame] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Flame] 怎么甩掉这家伙？
how do I get this guy off me?
[Flame] 兄弟，
Dude,
[Flame] 快把他弄走。
get this guy off me.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，这我真没辙。
I can't do anything about this, bro.
[Flame] 你简直…
You're like...
Yeah,
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
[Wemmbu] 可要是他追着你跑，
but if he's chasing you,
[Wemmbu] 我以为我能拉住仇恨
I thought like I can just like pull aggro
[Flame] 漂亮
Nice
[Wemmbu] 他还悬着呢。
He's still he's still hovering.
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，火力支援！情况不对！
Yo pop me fire is in strength fire isn't straight
[Flame] 好的
All
[Flame] 好的。
right,
[Flame] 你来搞定这家伙，
how about you take care of this dude,
[Flame] 我这就去会会这个BOSS
I'm gonna go imagine this boss
[Wemmbu] 好的。
Okay,
[Wemmbu] 我来拖住他就行
I mean I can just keep him distracted,
[Wemmbu] 但咱们迟早得钻地底去会会他。
but we'll have to deal with him eventually by going underground.
[Wemmbu] 好的
Okay
[Flame] 这帮家伙真够猛的。
All these guys are really badass.
[Wemmbu] 是啊，他们最近贼积极，
Yeah, like they've been picking up.
[Wemmbu] 东西捡个没完。
They've been picking up items
[Wemmbu] 但最难的是怎么闷声干成。
the lowkey is going to be the hardest part finishing it
[Wemmbu] 不行
no
[Wemmbu] 这算是个线索了
that's kind of a clue into that
[Flame] 哦，
Oh,
[Flame] 你的货就在这人手里。
this is the guy with your stuff.
[Wemmbu] 等等，谁啊？
Wait, who?
[Flame] XTremon
XTremon.
[Flame] 干掉他。
Kill him.
[Flame] 你的东西在他那儿。
He has your stuff.
[Flame] 那是在下，老铁。
That is me, buddy.
[Flame] 逮到他了。
Yeah, I'm on him.
[Wemmbu] 逮到了。
Got him.
[Wemmbu] 哦豁。
Oh, yeah.
[Wemmbu] 他就是个行走的宝箱怪。
He was a loot piñata.
[Flame] 拿上你的白色
Yeah, grab your white
[Flame] 潜影盒，快。
shulker box, quick.
[Flame] 我在努力，我在努力。
I'm trying, I'm trying.
[Wemmbu] 赶紧过来把东西运走。
Just come over here and cart the stuff,
[Wemmbu] 说实话。
honestly.
[Wemmbu] 我抓到了！天呐，我真逮住它了！
Oh, I caught it! Oh, my God, I actually got it!
[Wemmbu] 剩下的东西用矿车运走。
Cart the rest of the stuff.
[Wemmbu] 直接装箱，装箱，装箱。
Just cart it, cart it, cart it.
[Wemmbu] 剩下的人用矿车运走。
Cart the rest of the stuff.
[Wemmbu] 咱可不能让他们得手啊兄弟。
We can't let them get it dude.
[Wemmbu] 干掉这家伙。
Kill this guy.
[Flame] 逮着了，逮着了！
Got them, got them!
[Flame] 漂亮！
Nice!
[Wemmbu] 一堆人扎堆儿呢。
There's a bunch of guys just congregating.
[Wemmbu] 他们没发现咱们的藏身处。
They didn't know where we were.
[Wemmbu] 我要把他们全宰了。
I'm gonna kill them all.
[Wemmbu] 也就20。
It's only like 20.
[Wemmbu] 漂亮。
Nice.
[Wemmbu] 鞘翅重锤我包了，保真。
Okay, Elytra Mace are on me, certifiably.
[Flame] 鞘翅重锤我带了。
Elytra Mace are on me.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 鞘翅重锤还在附近，小心点。
The Elytra Mace are still nearby, watch out.
[Wemmbu] 等等，他没放蛛网，直接放了！
Wait, he didn't web, he just webs!
[Wemmbu] 不行！
No!
[Wemmbu] 我打错人了。
I hit the wrong guy.
[Wemmbu] 你打我干嘛。
You hit me.
[Wemmbu] 我打——不，
I hit- no,
[Wemmbu] 我-我-我在给这家伙搓澡呢。
I'm- I'm- I'm cleaning this guy,
[Wemmbu] 好嘞。
okay.
[Wemmbu] 我逮住——我逮住那个被你网住的家伙了。
I- I got the- I got a guy that you webbed,
[Flame] 但这并非鞘翅重锤。
but it wasn't the Elytra Mace.
[Wemmbu] 逮到他了
Got him
[Wemmbu] 方向反了，长官！找个好位置，快点！
it's just the other way sir find a fine a fine come on.
[Wemmbu] 我上了我上了
I'm on I'm on
[Wemmbu] 兄弟他老把我从天上打下来
Dude he keeps hitting me out of the sky road
[Flame] 他咋没在亮光里打爆它
How did he not pop it in the light on
[Flame] 兄弟，
Dude, like,
[Flame] 看吧，所以我才喜欢服务器现在没重锤了。
See, this is why I like the fact that there's no more maces on the server.
[Flame] 重锤对重锤简直蠢到家了。
Because mace versus mace is the stupidest thing ever.
[Wemmbu] 你刚才打我了！
Okay, so you just hit me!
[Flame] 兄弟，他偏偏这回在里头。
Dude, the one time he's in the thing.
[Wemmbu] 你守我啊，老铁！
You guarded me, dude!
[Wemmbu] 他刚撤你就护上我了！
He pulled out and then you guarded me!
Oh my god.
[Wemmbu] 哟，
Yo,
[Wemmbu] 伙计，他被蛛网缠住了！
buddy, he's in a web!
[Wemmbu] 走起！
Let's go!
[Flame] 现在不行。
Alright, not right now.
[Flame] 噢，我急需，急需那个...
Oh, I need, I need the...
[Wemmbu] 兄弟，罩着他！
Guard him, buddy!
[Wemmbu] 兄弟！
Buddy!
[Flame] 我去！
Oh my god!
[Wemmbu] 我...我啥也干不了。
Like, I... you can't do anything.
[Wemmbu] 你凭啥说我不行？！
What do you mean I can't do anything?!
[Wemmbu] 嘿，兄弟！
Here, buddy!
[Wemmbu] 我鞘翅坏了！
My Elytra is broken!
[Flame] 来，兄弟！
Here, buddy!
[Flame] 他...
He's...
[Flame] 他凉了...
he's dead...
[Flame] 我去，老天爷。
Dude, oh my God.
[Wemmbu] 老兄他一直卡进天花板
Dude he keeps glitching into the ceiling
[Flame] 这哥们咋把每个心都吃了？
Like how does bro eat every heart?
[Wemmbu] 太棒了！
YES!
[Wemmbu] 总算！天呐！
Finally! Oh my god!
[Wemmbu] 兄弟
Dude
[Wemmbu] 这人我服。
I'll give it to that guy,
[Wemmbu] 这家伙真难缠
he was tough to put down bro
[Flame] 我滴老天
Oh my god
[Flame] 这波涨了多少粉？
How much sub did you get from this?
[Wemmbu] 我怕是爆了一地装备
I probably lost a ton of stuff
[Flame] 装备全爆了？
You lost a ton of stuff?
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 你扒我装备？
Are you taking my armor?
[Wemmbu] 谢了。
Thank you.
[Flame] 兄弟，
Bro,
[Flame] 兄弟，你赚麻了。
you got so much, bro.
[Flame] 兄弟，有多的没？
You got spare, bro.
[Flame] 我去，
Dang,
[Flame] 他们真就，
they really,
[Flame] 喜欢，
like,
[Flame] 这块儿全乱套了。
messed up this whole area.
[Flame] 这也太离谱了。
It is crazy.
[Flame] 他们就好这口...
They really like...
[Wemmbu] 文化无处不在……
places culture every...
[Flame] 好的。
Alright.
[Wemmbu] 好的。
[Flame] 完事了？开打吧兄弟。
Now that this is over, let's fight, bro.
[Flame] 耶
Yeah
[Flame] 兄弟，加把劲。
Come on bro.
[Flame] 真没想到你居然找到了植物。
I didn't think you actually found a plant.
[Wemmbu] 我懂你绝不会放弃的伙计
I know you're never gonna give up dude
[Flame] 我刚破了你纪录
I just broke your one
[Flame] 哎哟 兄弟别这样
Oh come on bro
[Flame] 死太快了兄弟
Can't die this quick bro
[Flame] 至少跟我过两招
Give me a fight at least
[Wemmbu] 至少分我一口。
Give me a bite at least.
[Flame] 想得美。
Nope.
[Wemmbu] 哟，你试过了啊。
Oh, you tried it.
[Wemmbu] 你可真行。
You really tried it.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 你要召一堆狗去打空中的敌人？
You're going to summon a bunch of dogs against the aerial opponent?
[Flame] 踩我身上。
Land on me.
[Wemmbu] 这主意不错。
Seems like a good idea.
[Flame] 谅你也不敢。
I bet you won't.
[Wemmbu] 啊？啥？！
Oh, what?!
[Wemmbu] 全溜没影了。
And they're all gone now.
[Flame] 才不是呢。
No, they're not, actually.
[Flame] 盔甲就是干这个用的。
That's what the armor's for.
[Flame] 好的。
Okay.
[Wemmbu] 好嘞！
OK!
[Flame] 模组无限护盾！
Mod's infinite shield!
[Flame] 哈哈你真撞上了！
Haha you actually bumped!
[Flame] 哈哈！
Haha!
[Wemmbu] 我搞砸了。
I broke something.
[Flame] 最强玩家咋了？
What happened to the strongest player?
[Flame] 狗没了就跟我打？
Will you fight me if the dogs are gone?
[Flame] 想打架？我帮你炸飞他们。
I can blow them up for you if that means you'll fight.
[Flame] 还不够。
Not enough,
[Flame] 你连力气都没有！我能...
you don't even have strength! I can...
[Flame] 我全吃光啦！
I'm eating it all off!
[Flame] 还觉得自己是最强的？
You still think you're the strongest?
[Flame] 你压根就不是我的对手。
It's like you're physically not strong enough to beat me.
[Flame] 认我比你强就完事了。
We can be done here once you admit I'm stronger than you.
[Wemmbu] 啥？
What?
[Wemmbu] 你就打算用这招收场？
That's really what you want to end the fight with?
[Flame] 我是说...
I mean...
[Flame] 用不着宰你。
I don't really need to kill you.
[Flame] 我是说，我能...
I mean, I can...
[Flame] 想倒是想，不过...
if I want to, but...
[Flame] 我宁愿你干脆...
I'd rather you just...
[Flame] 明知你活着...
live with you knowing...
[Flame] 我更强。
that I'm better.
[Flame] 兄弟，你看...
Bro, look...
[Flame] 你啥也干不了！搞什么名堂？！
You can't do nothing! What are you doing?!
[Wemmbu] 我想凑齐一套装备...
I wanna get a full set of gear...
[Wemmbu] 然后呢...
and then...
[Wemmbu] 再跟Flamefrags比一场。
have a re-match with flamefrags.
[Flame] 你以为我没看见？
You didn't think I saw that?
[Wemmbu] 哦豁。
Oh, yeah.
[Wemmbu] 你瞧
You see,
[Wemmbu] 在Unstable SMP服务器上，
on the Unstable SMP,
[Wemmbu] 我超强的。
I'm one of the strongest players,
[Wemmbu] 少数耍重锤的玩家之一。
being one of the only mace wielders.
[Wemmbu] 但最近，
But lately,
[Wemmbu] 感觉我一直在输
it feels like I've done nothing but lose
[Wemmbu] 要么变强，要么被人踩。
or be weaker than people.
[Wemmbu] 所以就算有机会开溜，
So even when presented with the opportunity to leave,
[Wemmbu] 我得去探探路
I decided that I would need to explore
[Wemmbu] 比远境更远之境
even further beyond the Minecraft Farlands
[Wemmbu] 得想办法让自己变强点。
to discover some sort of way to become stronger myself.
[Wemmbu] 我懂这玩意儿。
I know what this is.
[Wemmbu] 这是个
It's a
[Wemmbu] 轨道炮无限连。
repeating pattern of orbital cannons.
[Wemmbu] 我是补货女神
I'm the Lady of Restock
[Wemmbu] 可一到那儿我就闲得发慌
But once I got there I was completely bored
[Wemmbu] 我在服务器上没事干了
I had nothing left to do on the server
[eggchan] 你咋不搞个假身份混进去呢兄弟？
Why don't you just like go under a false identity bro?
[MinuteTech] Flame可不是普通玩家。
Flame he's not an ordinary player.
[MinuteTech] 他哪会啊
He doesn't he
[MinuteTech] 输了不算完
doesn't end on a loss
[MinuteTech] 你俩可是这服里数一数二的高手
You two are some of the most powerful players on the server you
[MinuteTech] 为这破事较劲纯属浪费生命 哪天你俩都得搭进去
waste on this rivalry that's gonna get you both killed one day
[Flame] 嘿，兄弟。
Hello, bro.
[Wemmbu] 哟。
Yo.
[Flame] 还是说你承认我比你强了？
Or can you just admit that I'm stronger than you?
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Wemmbu] 你能
You can-
[Wemmbu] 我爱
I like-
[Wemmbu] 你也能成最强。
You can be the strongest.
[Flame] 就这？
That's it?
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼。
Yeah.
[Flame] 所以你现在不在乎了
so you don't care anymore
[Flame] 还是你终于发现差得远呢
or do you just finally realize that it's not close
[Flame] 你毫无胜算
that you don't stand a chance
[Wemmbu] 看来还是你最强
I guess not I guess you're the strongest
[Flame] 我是说
I mean like
[Wemmbu] 妥
yeah
[Flame] 切记
just remember that
[Wemmbu] 好的，我记住了。
OK, I'll remember.
[Flame] 他江山坐得稳。
He'll always be in power.
[Flame] 下回再来讨打
so next time you try and fight me
[Flame] 记好了，我技术比你强多了兄弟
just remember I'm more skilled than you bro
[Flame] 所以
so
[Flame] 别来丢人现眼
just don't even step up
[Wemmbu] 你比我牛也没事
you can be more skilled than me that's fine
[Flame] 那我先溜了
well I guess I'm gonna go home
[Flame] 打不过就溜
GG's I guess
[Wemmbu] 我猜错了
I broke, I guess
[Flame] 我是说
I mean
[Flame] 确实
yeah I mean
[Flame] 没成
it wasn't
[Flame] 真有意思
very interesting
[Flame] 我是说
I mean
[Flame] 是个-
Is a-
[Flame] 基地与轨道站。
Bases and orbitals.
[Wemmbu] 嗯哼
yeah
[Wemmbu] 回头见
alright see you man
[Flame] 好的
alright
[Wemmbu] 你要退语音群不
you gonna leave the voice chat group or
[Flame] 哦我忘了我们在群里
oh I forgot we were in the group
[Flame] 哦我忘了我们在组队
[Flame] 好的
okay
[Wemmbu] 好嘞
yeah
[LettuceK] 嘿，哥们
Hey buddy
[Wemmbu] 你好
hello
[LettuceK] 哇哦
wow
[LettuceK] 你这模样可真够惨的
you've definitely seen better days
[Wemmbu] 这啥意思
so what's that supposed to mean
[LettuceK] 刚才那波够刺激
that was that was quite
[LettuceK] 这场面可真够劲爆的！
that was that was quite the spectacle!
[LettuceK] 感觉你有点飘
You feel like you
[LettuceK] 这处境可真不咋地。
definitely been in a better situation,
[LettuceK] 不？
no?
[LettuceK] 多谢啦。
Thanks for this, by the way.
[Wemmbu] 呃...
Uh...
[LettuceK] 总之呢...
Anyways...
[Wemmbu] 咦...所以...你的
Huh. So... your
[Wemmbu] 全军覆没。
entire army just died.
[LettuceK] 难受吧？
It's unfortunate right?
[LettuceK] 可你现在这德行，
But with the way you are right now,
[LettuceK] 我一个人就能把你收拾了。
I don't even think I need an army to take you with me.
[LettuceK] 所以，
So,
[LettuceK] 这下可热闹了
what's going to happen now is that
[LettuceK] 要么死路一条，要么跟我走。
either you're going to die or you're going to come with me.
谢啦。
Thank you.